$TNG_Gnl	General
$TNG_Rac	Race groups
$TNG_Add	Addons
$TNG_S52	Slot 52 Mods
$TNG_Adv	Advanced
	
$TNG_TRS	Reset to default
$TNG_TNT	No genital
	
$TNG_TCT	Circumcised
$TNG_TMT	Muscular-Style 1
$TNG_TM2	Muscular-Style 2
$TNG_TRT	Regular-Style 1
$TNG_TR2	Regular-Style 2
	
$TNG_TCT (d)	Circumcised (d)
$TNG_TMT (d)	Muscular-Style 1 (d)
$TNG_TM2 (d)	Muscular-Style 2 (d)
$TNG_TRT (d)	Regular-Style 1 (d)
$TNG_TR2 (d)	Regular-Style 2 (d)
	
$TNG_TCT (s)	Circumcised (s)
$TNG_TMT (s)	Muscular-Style 1 (s)
$TNG_TM2 (s)	Muscular-Style 2 (s)
$TNG_TRT (s)	Regular-Style 1 (s)
$TNG_TR2 (s)	Regular-Style 2 (s)
	
$TNG_SOH	Default Sizes
$TNG_SRS	Reset Size
$TNG_SDC	Do not change
$TNG_SXS	X-Small
$TNG_S_S	Small
$TNG_S_M	Medium
$TNG_S_L	Large
$TNG_SXL	X-Large
	
$TNG_GNT	Notifications
	
$TNG_KyH	Controls
$TNG_DAK	Integration with DAK
$TNG_DKN	DAK integration has been removed. This can cause conflicts between the assigned keys with other mods. Do you want to reset all of them?
$TNG_K_N	Addon/Size Customization
$TNG_K_R	Swap Revealing/Covering
$TNG_K_U	Raise genital
$TNG_K_D	Lower genital
$TNG_KAL	TNG actor lock on:
$TNG_KAR	Released actor lock
	
$TNG_OGT	Genital Type
$TNG_OGS	Genital Size Multiplier
	
$TNG_AMR	Randomize men addons
$TNG_AWC	Women chance for an addon
$TNG_ASS	Select the size:
$TNG_AST	Select the addon:
$TNG_ASA	Select the armor:
$TNG_A_W	Gentlewomen Addons
$TNG_A_M	Gentlemen Addons
$TNG_ANW	There seems to be no addons installed for women!
$TNG_ANM	There seems to be no addons installed for men!
	
$TNG_52D	For these body armor:
$TNG_52C	Hides genitalia
$TNG_52R	Reveals genitalia
$TNG_52U	Let me to choose
$TNG_52N	No conflicting mods with slot 52 found!
	
$TNG_Yes	Yes
$TNG__No	No
	
$TNG_N_1	Could not find a relevant armor!
$TNG_N_2	The armor was handled successfully!
$TNG_N_3	The armor cannot be modified!
$TNG_N_4	There are no addons for the current NPC!
	
$TNG_W_1	No actor can be selected!
$TNG_W_3	DAK Integration is enabled but relevant information cannot be found. Please open MCM and disable DAK integration.
	
$TNG_E_0	The New Gentleman DLL cannot be loaded successfully! Make sure you have all the requirements installed!
	
$TNG_WN1	The current race cannot be modified by TNG.
$TNG_WN2	The current actor cannot be modified by TNG.
$TNG_WN3	The selected addon cannot be used.
$TNG_WN4	TNG internal issue handling the armor.
$TNG_WN5	The NPC current skin does not allow any modifications.
$TNG_WN6	The player size cannot be modified due to the option in MCM.
$TNG_WN7	The skeleton is missing the bones for genitalia. TNG won't modify the race!
$TNG_WN8	The actor's race is not supported by TNG.
$TNG_WN9	TNG faced an internal error. If the error can be reproduced, please report this error on the mod page as a bug report!
	
$TNG_WPT	The players genital addon was reverted to original to avoid issues.
$TNG_WPS	The players genital size was reverted to original to avoid issues.
	
$TNG_HGD	To avoid hotkey conflicts you can use the key from Dynamic activation key in combination with the selected keys below to activate them.
$TNG_HGC	Double check for clipping issues when an armor is equipped.
$TNG_HGF	Automatically mark armor on female characters to revealing if they have an item equipped on slot 52. Note that if armor is shared between men and women, it would also become revealing for men.
$TNG_HGM	Automatically mark armor on male characters to revealing if they have an item equipped on slot 52. Note that if armor is shared between men and women, it would also become revealing for women.
$TNG_HGN	Show or hide notifications on the hud.
$TNG_HGE	Leave player size to be modified in the race menu using the XP32 racemenu addon.
$TNG_HKU	Move the genital up or down. If there is an NPC with genital under the cursor it would move the NPC's genital, otherwise the player's.
$TNG_HKN	Customize player or NPCs addon and size. If there is an NPC under cursor it would customize the NPC, otherwise it would customize the player.
$TNG_HKS	Swap revealing/covering
$TNG_H_S	Changes the size category multiplier. Each actor gets a size category randomly and can be customized using the customization key. Their final genital size would be: (their race multiplier) * (their size category)
$TNG_HOA	Set the default addon for the race. You can further customize NPCs using the customization keyword. (For race group info hold Left Alt)
$TNG_HOS	Changes the race multiplier on top of NPCs size category. The final multiplier for each NPC: [race multiplier] * [size category multiplier].  (For race group info hold Left Alt)
$TNG_HAC	The chance that women receive any of the selected addons below.
$TNG_HAD	Whether to distribute this addon to NPCs. All addons are always available in customization menu.
$TNG_HLF	If you click, a message the local folder on your device where the TNG log (and other SKSE logs) are saved.
$TNG_HLL	The level of the information that is logged. Don't change it unless you think that is necessary!
$TNG_H52	Default behavior to treat the conflicting mods.
$TNG_HMR	Set behavior to neglect conflict(unchecked) or to treat the mod as a revealing mod(checked).
$TNG_HRM	Randomizes men genitalia with a higher chance for racial addon
$TNG_HPU	If your player addon disappears after load, enable this option. (Forced active with RSV)
$TNG_HPN	(Experimental) If your NPC addons disappears after load, enable this option. (Forced active with RSV)
$TNG_HLD	(Experimental) The key to find issues when actors do not have genitalia or their genitalia is visible through armor
$TNG_HPR	Show all compatible races in the MCM. By default TNG filters non-playable races that have less than 5 NPCs
$TNG_HZZ	(Experimental) Go to bed compatibility
	
$TNG_GPH	Player extra options
$TNG_GAD	Compatibility
$TNG_GPC	Check after load
$TNG_GEP	Don't change size
$TNG_GNP	Check NPCs regularly
$TNG_GPR	Show every race
$TNG_GZZ	Go To Bed
	
$TNG_L_H	Logging
$TNG_L_T	Log level
$TNG_L_D	Show log directory
$TNG_LDN	Log directory not found
$TNG_LLD	Debug
$TNG_LLI	Info(Default)
$TNG_LLW	Warnings and worse
$TNG_LLE	Errors and worse
$TNG_LLC	Critical
$TNG_LLO	Off
	
	
$TNG_P_K	Debugging key
$TNG_P_0	Never mind
$TNG_P_1	I can see the genital through clothes!
$TNG_P_2	I cannot see the genital!
$TNG_PD0	No issues found with the actor. If you see an issue, please report it.
$TNG_PD1	An issue was found with the actor. TNG tried to fix it. If the issue is widespread among NPCs, please report it.
$TNG_PD2	An issue was found with the actor and TNG could not fix it. Please report it.
$TNG_PD9	The current actor cannot be evaluated!
	
$TNG_PA1	The current actor is not wearing any covering items!
$TNG_PA2	The current actor is equipping an item on slot 52 which covers genital.!
$TNG_PA3	The current actor is excluded! Use NPC customization key to reset their addon, and it should re-appear!
$TNG_PA4	The current actor is a woman and you didn't set women chance to 100!
$TNG_PA5	The current actor's race is set to have no addons in the MCM menu!
$TNG_PA6	The current actor is wearing a piece of covering items!
