$ShovelsBuryBodies	Shovels Bury Bodies
$BODY_HELP{}	Click this option to search, move, or delete {}.
$Configuration_Page	Configuration
$BurialDuration	Burial Duration
$BurialDurationConfiguration_Help	How many seconds it takes to bury bodies.
$BuriedBodies_Header	Buried Bodies
$Maintenance_Page	Maintenance
$AutoloadSettings_Header	Autoload Settings
$Enabled	Enabled
$EnabledMaintenance_Help	Uncheck this option if you want mod-specific variables not to be loaded. This does not apply to variables in the settings file and when the script is upgraded to a newer version. Disabling this option is useful when there are conflicts with other mods during autoload.
$LoadingDelay	Loading Delay
$LoadingDelayMaintenance_Help	Settings loading delay in seconds. Useful if the mod takes time to initialize.
$LoadSettings	Load Settings
$LoadSettingsMaintenance_Help	Forces the modification to reload the settings. Useful if autoloading is disabled.
$ResetSettings	Reset Settings
$ResetSettingsMaintenance_Help	Reset settings to default values.
$LoadSettingsonReload	Load Settings on Reload
$LoadSettingsonReloadMaintenance_Help	Check this option if you want the settings to be loaded every time you load the game. Useful if you have something that reverts settings. This option will not work if the base mod does not use the OnGameReload event or if you disabled Autoload.
$Verbose	Verbose
$VerboseMaintenance_Help	Check this option to see additional information during loader work.
