; Controller Script
$FF_ResetHorseDo	Setting Follower Horses
$FF_ResetHorseDone	Setting Follower Horses
$FF_WarnInSlots	Follower is already in the Framework
$FF_WarnTooMany	You have the maximum number of Followers
$FF_WarnInvalid	This Follower is not in the Framework
$FF_WarnImport	There are no open Slots for Adding a Follower
$FF_AllDisStart	Dismissing Followers...
$FF_AllDisEnd	Followers Dismissed
$FF_AllRemoveStart	Removing Followers...
$FF_AllRemoveEnd	Followers Removed
$FF_AllWaiting	All Followers are Waiting
$FF_AllFollow	All Followers are Following
$FF_SortingStart	Sorting Follower Slots...
$FF_SortingEnd	Follower Slots Sorted
$FF_FlushStart	Flushing Follower Slots...
$FF_FlushEnd	Follower Slots Flushed
$FF_HomeStart	Updating Home Bases
$FF_HomeEnd	Home Bases Updated

$FF_StartTasks	(NFF) Performing Startup Tasks...
$FF_ResetRequired	Quest Reset and Follower Dismissal Required...
$FF_AddBasesSlots	Adjusting Home Bases
$FF_EndTasks	(NFF) Startup Tasks Complete.
$FF_StartRefreshWpn	Refreshing Weapons...
$FF_EndRefreshWpn	Weapons Refreshed.
$FF_StartHorses	Applying Horse Changes...
$FF_ConvertedOutfits	Outfit System Ready
$FF_EndHorses	Changes Complete.
$FF_NoSpell	No spell is equipped.
$FF_StartRelax	Followers are relaxing
$FF_EndRelax	Followers no longer relaxed
$FF_FrameworkReady	Follower Framework Ready.
$FF_WarnSellMagic	Followers cannot sell enchanted items.
$FF_WarnOutfitItem	You can't use that in an outfit.
$FF_ClearedAlias	Found Alias. Clearing...
$FF_ResetDefaults	Clearing factions and resetting defaults...
$FF_ReturnSale	Returning unsold items to the player...
$FF_FollowersAttacking	Followers are Attacking
$FF_FollowersRetreating	Followers are Retreating
$FF_FollowersRetreatingCancel	Followers stopped Retreating
$FF_FollowersNoTarget	All Attack: No Target
$FF_FollowersRetreat	Retreat/Pacify All
$FF_FollowersRetreatCancel	Stop Retreat All
$FF_FolBaseRemove	Follower removed from Home Bases
$FF_FolAssignBase	Follower assigned to Home Base
$FF_FolBaseRemSel	Remove from Home Bases
$FF_OutfitMax	There are already a maximum number of outfits in use.

$FF_OutfitMovedPlayer	Outfit Items were moved to your inventory
$FF_OutfitMovedPChest	Outfit Items were moved to the Player Chest
$FF_SatchelMoved	Satchel Items were moved to your inventory
$FF_ExtraMovedPChest	Items were moved to the Player Chest

$FF_SlotGameFill	Game Slot is now occupied
$FF_SlotGameClear	Game Slot is now cleared
$FF_ExitMCMMsg	Please Exit the MCM Menu to finalize.

$FF_ResetMainStart	Starting Framework Reset. Please Wait...
$FF_ResetRemove	...Followers Removed.
$FF_ResetDFQuest	...Follower Quest Restarted.
$FF_ResetMainEnd	Framework Reset Complete.
$FF_ResetMainEnd2	Recommend: Save then Load your Saved Game.

$FF_RestartQuest	Restarting Follower Quest...

; Home Base messages
$FF_HomeSet	Home Base Set
$FF_WorkSet	Work Location Set
$FF_RelaxSet	Relax Location Set

$FF_RangeSetClose	Follower Set to Close Range
$FF_RangeSetCloseAll	Followers Set to Close Range
$FF_RangeSetMed	Follower Set to Medium Range
$FF_RangeSetMedAll	Followers Set to Medium Range
$FF_RangeSetFar	Follower Set to Far Range
$FF_RangeSetFarAll	Followers Set to Far Range

$FF_RangeSetCloseCbt	Follower Set to Close Combat Range
$FF_RangeSetCloseAllCbt	Followers Set to Close Combat Range
$FF_RangeSetMedCbt	Follower Set to Medium Combat Range
$FF_RangeSetMedAllCbt	Followers Set to Medium Combat Range
$FF_RangeSetFarCbt	Follower Set to Far Combat Range
$FF_RangeSetFarAllCbt	Followers Set to Far Combat Range

$FF_RoleSet	Follower Role Set
$FF_CombatStyleSet	Follower Combat Style Set
$FF_CombatStyleWarn	Cannot Set Combat on Non-Unique Actor

; Pop-up Menus
$FF_Exit	[Exit]
$FF_All	- ALL -
$FF_Refresh	(Refresh)

$FF_TakeTorches	Take All Torches
$FF_GiveTorches	Return All Torches
$FF_RefreshGear	Refresh All Adventuring Gear
$FF_ToggleWeaponAll	Weapons only in Combat (All)
$FF_ToggleShieldAll	Shield only in Combat (All)

; Menu Choices All
$FF_AllWaitFollow	Wait/Follow/Behind All >
$FF_InventoryLoot	Loot/Inventory >
$FF_SummonAll	Summon >
$FF_SandboxToggle	Sandbox Toggle
$FF_HistoryFav	History/Favorites/Slots >
$FF_RangeAll	Set Range All >
$FF_TraitsAll	Set Traits All >
$FF_DmgMultAll	Dynamic Damage Mult >
$FF_DismissAll	Dismiss All

$FF_AllFollowRange	Follow Range All >
$FF_AllCombatRange	Combat Range All >
$FF_ShowHistory	Show History
$FF_SubSingle	Command Single >

; Menu Choices Single

$FF_DoFavor	Do Favor
$FF_Recruit	Recruit
$FF_WaitFollow	Wait/Follow >
$FF_Extras	Extras >
$FF_IsWaiting	Is Waiting for You
$FF_IsFollowing	Is Following You
$FF_Range	Range >
$FF_FollowClose	Follow Range: Close >
$FF_FollowMed	Follow Range: Medium >
$FF_FollowFar	Follow Range: Far >
$FF_CombatClose	Combat Range: Close >
$FF_CombatMed	Combat Range: Medium >
$FF_CombatFar	Combat Range: Far >
$FF_EnforceRangeOn	Enforce Combat Range (On)
$FF_EnforceRangeOff	Enforce Combat Range (Off)
$FF_Traits	Traits >
$FF_SetCraft	Crafting >
$FF_SetHomeBase	Set Home Base >
$FF_SendHome	Send Home (Teleport)
$FF_CraftTorchOn	Craft Torches (On)
$FF_CraftTorchOff	Craft Torches (Off)
$FF_CraftArrowsOn	Craft Arrows (On)
$FF_CraftBoltsOn	Craft Bolts (On)
$FF_CraftArrowsOff	Craft Arrows (Off)
$FF_CraftPotionsOn	Craft Potions (On)
$FF_CraftPotionsOff	Craft Potions (Off)
$FF_SharpWeaponsOn	Sharpen Weapons (On)
$FF_SharpWeaponsOff	Sharpen Weapons (Off)
$FF_DrinkOn	Drink at Tavern (On)
$FF_DrinkOff	Drink at Tavern (Off)
$FF_LoadSaveTweaks	Load/Save Settings >
$FF_SaveFol	Save Follower Settings
$FF_LoadFol	Load Follower Settings
$FF_LoadSaveTitle	Load/Save Settings

$FF_Equip	Set Outfit/Inventory >
$FF_Teach	Teach Spell >
$FF_TeachInvalid	Teach Spell (None)
$FF_Dismiss	Dismiss
$FF_Push	Push (Fix Glitch)
$FF_SubAll	Command All >

; Menu Titles
$FF_CommandAll	Command All
$FF_Followers	Followers
$FF_WaitMenu	Wait/Follow/Behind
$FF_RangeTitle	Range
$FF_FollowRange	Follow Range
$FF_CombatRange	Combat Range
$FF_TeachTitle	Teach Spell
$FF_EquipTitle	Outfit/Inventory
$FF_CraftTitle	Crafting/Interaction
$FF_TraitsTitle	Traits
$FF_DmgMultTitle	Dynamic Damage Mult
$FF_HeadwearTitle	Headwear

$FF_SkillTitle	Skills (sorted)
$FF_SkillMenu	Skills >

$FF_SpellTitle	Spells
$FF_SpellMenu	Spells >
$FF_BuffSharpen	Sharpened Weapon (Buff)
$FF_BuffCourage	Courage (Buff)
$FF_BuffInspired	Inspired (Buff)

$FF_InvTitle	Inventory
$FF_InvMenu	Inventory >

$FF_HistoryFavTitle	History/Favorites
$FF_ExtrasTitle	Extras

$FF_SummonTitle	Summon Followers
$FF_FavoritesTitle{}	Favorites ({})
$FF_Favorites	Show Favorites >
$FF_HistoryTitle{}	History ({})
$FF_LootTitle	Loot/Inventory

$FF_RenCategory	Rename Category
$FF_RemCategory	Remove Category

$FF_FavDefault	Default Favorites
$FF_FavEmpty	Empty

$FF_FavoritesMax	You are at the Maximum of 25 Favorites
$FF_FavoritesAdded	Follower Added to Favorites
$FF_FavoritesRemoved	Favorite Follower Removed
$FF_FavoriteRemove	Remove Favorite Follower
$FF_FavoriteAdd	Add to Favorites >
$FF_FavoriteFull	(Favorites are Full)

$FF_FavoritesAdjust	Removed one or more Invalid Followers from Favorites
$FF_FavPortM	Call Favorites to You
$FF_FavPort	Favorite Followers Called
$FF_FavWaitingM	All Favorites Wait
$FF_FavWaiting	Favorite Followers are Waiting
$FF_FavFollowM	All Favorites Follow
$FF_FavRecruitAM	All Favorites Recruit (Add)
$FF_FavRecruitSM	All Favorites Recruit (Swap)
$FF_FavRecruitA	Favorites Recruited
$FF_FavRecruitS	Favorites Swapped-In
$FF_FavFollow	Favorite Followers are Following

$FF_AllWait	All Wait
$FF_AllFollowM	All Follow
$FF_AllBehind	All Behind Me
$FF_AllSnap	All Snap Out of It
$FF_Wait	Wait
$FF_Follow	Follow
$FF_Behind	Behind Me

$FF_AllRangeClose	All Close
$FF_AllRangeMedium	All Medium
$FF_AllRangeFar	All Far
$FF_RangeClose	Close
$FF_RangeMedium	Medium
$FF_RangeFar	Far

$FF_TeachNoneR	Teach (Right): None
$FF_TeachNoneL	Teach (Left): None

$FF_Trade	Trade
$FF_OpenStorage	Open Follower Storage
$FF_SellItems	Sell Items
$FF_SetGear	Set Outfit

$FF_HeadwearOff	Stored Headwear: Off >
$FF_HeadwearNone	Stored Headwear: None >
$FF_HeadSetNone	Set to: None
$FF_HeadSetCurrent	Set to Current: None
$FF_HeadCombatOn	Headwear only in Combat (On)
$FF_HeadCombatOff	Headwear only in Combat (Off)
$FF_NoHelmOn	Never Equip Headwear (On)
$FF_NoHelmOff	Never Equip Headwear (Off)

$FF_ShieldOff	Stored Shield: Off >
$FF_ShieldNone	Stored Shield: None >
$FF_ShieldCombatOn	Shield only in Combat (On)
$FF_ShieldCombatOff	Shield only in Combat (Off)
$FF_ShieldTitle	Shield
$FF_ShieldApplied	Shield Setting Applied

$FF_Undress	Undress
$FF_Redress	Redress

$FF_RoleStandard	Combat Role: Standard >
$FF_RoleHealer	Combat Role: Healer >
$FF_RoleTank	Combat Role: Tank >
$FF_Role_0	Standard
$FF_Role_1	Healer
$FF_Role_2	Tank

$FF_Unaggressive	Aggression: Unaggressive >
$FF_Aggressive	Aggression: Aggressive >
$FF_Aggression1	Unaggressive
$FF_Aggression2	Aggressive
$FF_AggressionAll	All Aggression >
$FF_AggressionSet	Follower Aggression Set
$FF_AggressionSetAll	Followers Aggression Set

$FF_AssistNobody	Assistance: Nobody >
$FF_AssistAllies	Assistance: Allies >
$FF_AssistFriends	Assistance: Friends/Allies >
$FF_Assist1	Helps Nobody
$FF_Assist2	Helps Allies
$FF_Assist3	Helps Friends/Allies
$FF_AssistAll	All Assistance >
$FF_AssistSet	Follower Assistance Set
$FF_AssistSetAll	Followers Assistance Set

$FF_ConCoward	Confidence: Coward >
$FF_ConCautious	Confidence: Cautious >
$FF_ConAverage	Confidence: Average >
$FF_ConBrave	Confidence: Brave >
$FF_ConFoolhardy	Confidence: Foolhardy >
$FF_ConAll	All Confidence >
$FF_ConSet	Follower Confidence Set
$FF_ConSetAll	Followers Confidence Set

$FF_Confidence1	Cowardly
$FF_Confidence2	Cautious
$FF_Confidence3	Average
$FF_Confidence4	Brave
$FF_Confidence5	Foolhardy

$FF_MoralAny	Morality: Any Crime >
$FF_MoralEnemy	Morality: Enemy/Property >
$FF_MoralProperty	Morality: Property >
$FF_MoralNo	Morality: No Crime >
$FF_MoralSet	Follower Morality Set
$FF_MoralSetAll	Followers Morality Set

$FF_Morality1	Any Crime
$FF_Morality2	Enemy/Property
$FF_Morality3	Property
$FF_Morality4	No Crime
$FF_MoralityAll	All Morality >

$FF_CStyle0	Combat Style: Default >
$FF_CStyle1	Combat Style: Mercenary >
$FF_CStyle2	Combat Style: Defender >
$FF_CStyle3	Combat Style: Berserker >
$FF_CStyle4	Combat Style: Archer >
$FF_CStyle5	Combat Style: Ranger >
$FF_CStyle6	Combat Style: Spellsword >
$FF_CStyle7	Combat Style: Wizard >
$FF_CStyle8	Combat Style: Magician >
$FF_CStyle9	Combat Style: Priest >
$FF_CStyle10	Combat Style: Balanced >
$FF_CStyle11	Combat Style: Arcane Archer >
$FF_CStyle12	Combat Style: War Priest >
$FF_CombatStyle1	Mercenary
$FF_CombatStyle2	Defender
$FF_CombatStyle3	Berserker
$FF_CombatStyle4	Archer
$FF_CombatStyle5	Ranger
$FF_CombatStyle6	Spellsword
$FF_CombatStyle7	Wizard
$FF_CombatStyle8	Magician
$FF_CombatStyle9	Priest
$FF_CombatStyle10	Balanced
$FF_CombatStyle11	Arcane Archer
$FF_CombatStyle12	War Priest

$FF_LootingTypeOff	Looting: Off >
$FF_LootingType0	Looting: Gold >
$FF_LootingType1	Looting: Ammo >
$FF_LootingType2	Looting: Food >
$FF_LootingType3	Looting: Potions >
$FF_LootingType4	Looting: Ingredients >
$FF_LootingType5	Looting: Miscellaneous >
$FF_LootingType6	Looting: Weapons/Ammo/Armor >
$FF_LootingType7	Looting: Armor >
$FF_LootingType8	Looting: Weapons >
$FF_LootingType9	Looting: Books >
$FF_LootingType10	Looting: Plants >

$FF_LootingTitle	Looting
$FF_LootingOffOn	None (Active)
$FF_LootingOn0	Gold (Active)
$FF_LootingOn1	Ammo (Active)
$FF_LootingOn2	Food (Active)
$FF_LootingOn3	Potions (Active)
$FF_LootingOn4	Ingredients (Active)
$FF_LootingOn5	Miscellaneous (Active)
$FF_LootingOn6	Weapons/Ammo/Armor (Active)
$FF_LootingOn7	Armor (Active)
$FF_LootingOn8	Weapons (Active)
$FF_LootingOn9	Books (Active)
$FF_LootingOn10	Plants (Active)

$FF_LootingOff	None
$FF_Looting0	Gold
$FF_Looting1	Ammo
$FF_Looting2	Food
$FF_Looting3	Potions
$FF_Looting4	Ingredients
$FF_Looting5	Miscellaneous
$FF_Looting6	Weapons/Ammo/Armor
$FF_Looting7	Armor
$FF_Looting8	Weapons
$FF_Looting9	Books
$FF_Looting10	Plants

$FF_SendLootType0	Send Loot: Inventory >
$FF_SendLootType1	Send Loot: Follower Storage >
$FF_SendLootType1alt	Send Loot: Clothing Satchel >
$FF_SendLootType2	Send Loot: Player Chest >
$FF_SendLootTypeOff	Send Loot: Off >

$FF_SendLoot_0	Normal Inventory
$FF_SendLootOn_0	Normal Inventory (Active)
$FF_SendLoot_1	Follower Storage
$FF_SendLoot_1alt	Clothing Satchel
$FF_SendLootOn_1	Follower Storage (Active)
$FF_SendLootOn_1alt	Clothing Satchel (Active)
$FF_SendLoot_2	Player Chest
$FF_SendLootOn_2	Player Chest (Active)

; Generic Menus
$FF_On	On
$FF_OnSilent	On, Silent
$FF_Off	Off
$FF_Cancel	- Cancel -
$FF_Back	< Back

; UILIB
$FF_BuildHistory	Reading History...

; Miscellaneous
$FF_ClickReset	Click to Reset
$FF_ClickView	Click to View
$FF_Visit	Visit
$FF_Tamriel	Tamriel
$FF_Teleporting	Teleporting...
$FF_CallFollower	Calling...
$FF_TorchesTaken	Follower Torches Taken
$FF_TorchesGiven	Follower Torches Given
$FF_OpenSell	Opening Selling Window...
$FF_Undressing	Undressing Follower...
$FF_Redressing	Redressing Follower...
$FF_PortOut	Porting on Exit
$FF_PortIn	Calling on Exit
$FF_CallToYou	Call to You
$FF_CallAllToYou	Call All to You
$FF_TravelTo	Fast Travel to
$FF_None	None
$FF_CanMarry	This NPC can now be married.
$FF_CanElope	You can elope with this NPC.
$FF_IsMarry	This NPC is already marriage eligible.
$FF_CantMarry	This NPC is not marriage eligible.
$FF_CanFollower	This NPC can now be a follower.
$FF_IsFollower	This NPC can already be a follower.
$FF_CantFollower	This NPC cannot be made into a follower.
$FF_HeadwearStored	Headwear Stored
$FF_HeadwearCleared	Headwear Cleared
$FF_HeadwearApplied	Headwear Setting Applied

; marriage
$FF_AreMarried	Congratulations on your marriage!
$FF_AreMarriedAdd	Congratulations on your latest marriage!
$FF_AreDivorced	You are now divorced.
$FF_AreDivorcedAdd	You now have 1 fewer spouse.

$FF_MountStyle1	No Support
$FF_MountStyle2	Spawned Horses
$FF_MountStyle3	Riding Support Only

$FF_HorseFX1	None
$FF_HorseFX2	Fire
$FF_HorseFX3	Frost
$FF_HorseFX4	Ghost
$FF_HorseFX5	Shadow

$FF_LightFX0	Vanilla/Modded
$FF_LightFX1	Soft Cold
$FF_LightFX2	Soft Warm
$FF_LightFX3	Soft Neutral
$FF_LightFX4	Do Not Cast

$FF_Skill1	Alchemy
$FF_Skill2	Alteration
$FF_Skill3	Block
$FF_Skill4	Conjuration
$FF_Skill5	Destruction
$FF_Skill6	Enchanting
$FF_Skill7	Heavy Armor
$FF_Skill8	Illusion
$FF_Skill9	Light Armor
$FF_Skill10	Lockpicking
$FF_Skill11	Archery
$FF_Skill12	One-Handed
$FF_Skill13	Pickpocket
$FF_Skill14	Restoration
$FF_Skill15	Smithing
$FF_Skill16	Sneak
$FF_Skill17	Speechcraft
$FF_Skill18	Two-Handed

; Translators - if alchemy or skill boosts perks tweaks given to follower as a perk
$FF_PerkAlc	Alchemy Skill Boosts
$FF_PerkSkill	General Skill Boosts

$FF_Resist1	Damage
$FF_Resist2	Disease
$FF_Resist3	Poison
$FF_Resist4	Fire
$FF_Resist5	Electric
$FF_Resist6	Frost
$FF_Resist7	Magic

$FF_UseDefault	Default

$FF_BoxRadius1	1024.0 units
$FF_BoxRadius2	2048.0 units
$FF_BoxRadius3	4096.0 units

$FF_NoClassSupport	Not Unique

$FF_Class0	- Cancel -
$FF_Class1	Assassin
$FF_Class2	Barbarian
$FF_Class3	Mage Conjurer
$FF_Class4	Mage Destruction
$FF_Class5	Mage Elemental
$FF_Class6	Mage Necro
$FF_Class7	Monk
$FF_Class8	Mystic
$FF_Class9	Nightblade
$FF_Class10	Nightingale
$FF_Class11	Ranger
$FF_Class12	Rogue
$FF_Class13	Scout
$FF_Class14	Sorcerer
$FF_Class15	Spellsword
$FF_Class16	Thief
$FF_Class17	Warrior 1H
$FF_Class18	Warrior 2H
$FF_Class19	Witchblade

$FF_HorseG	Use Global
$FF_Horse0	Brown
$FF_Horse1	Black
$FF_Horse2	Black & White
$FF_Horse3	Grey
$FF_Horse4	Palomino
$FF_Horse5	Shadow
$FF_Horse6	Cairn
$FF_HorseRnd	Random Pick

; MCM ------------------

$FF_ModName	NFF

$FF_Title	Nether's Follower Framework
$FF_Version	Follower Framework Version

$FF_Page1	Activity
$FF_Page2	Gameplay
$FF_Page3	Interaction
$FF_Page4	System
$FF_Page5	Follower Tweaks
$FF_Page6	Follower Stats
$FF_Page7	Follower Perks
$FF_Page8	Follower Abilities
$FF_Page9	Follower Outfit & Gear
$FF_Page10	Home Bases
$FF_Page11	Slots & History

$FF_TitlePage1	Follower Framework - Activity
$FF_TitlePage2	Follower Framework - Gameplay
$FF_TitlePage3	Follower Framework - Quest & Dialogue
$FF_TitlePage4	Follower Framework - System
$FF_TitlePage5	Follower Framework - Follower Tweaks
$FF_TitlePage6	Follower Framework - Follower Stats
$FF_TitlePage7	Follower Framework - Follower Perks
$FF_TitlePage8	Follower Framework - Follower Abilities
$FF_TitlePage9	Follower Framework - Follower Outfit & Gear
$FF_TitlePage10	Follower Framework - Home Bases
$FF_TitlePage11	Follower Framework - Slots & History


; DIALOGUE STRINGS --

$FF_SayAnimalRecruit	Hey pup, want to come along?
$FF_SayTrade	I need to trade some things with you.
$FF_SayBehind	Would you mind getting behind me?
$FF_SayBladesRecruit	I'd like to recruit you into the Blades.
$FF_SayBladesDeny	I'd rather not recruit you into the Blades.
$FF_SayCheckCount	I think there's room in my group for you.
$FF_SayDivorceInitial	I think we should call the marriage off.
$FF_SayDivorceJoke	I was just kidding.
$FF_SayDivorceFinal	I just don't think we should be together.
$FF_SayExpel	I no longer need your help (Expel).
$FF_SayExport	[Remove from Framework (Export)]
$FF_SayStewardRemove	I don't need you to be my steward any longer.
$FF_SayDismissFamily	I think it's time you for you to go home.
$FF_SayDismissGuard	I no longer need your services.
$FF_SayDoSomething	I need you to do something.
$FF_SayFollow	Follow me.
$FF_SayShowYou	Yes. Let me show you.
$FF_SayNeverMind	No. Never mind.
$FF_SayRecruitNo	On second thought, nevermind.
$FF_SayRecruitFamily	Want to come on an adventure with me?
$FF_SayRecruitAgain	Care to join me again?
$FF_SayRecruitGuard	I'd like to hire you to accompany me.
$FF_SayWait	Wait Here.
$FF_SayImport	[Add to Framework (Import)]
$FF_SayDivorceSorry	I'm sorry how things turned out.
$FF_SayPayExplain	About your pay...
$FF_SayPayBroke	I can't spare any gold in order to pay you.
$FF_SayPayGold	Here's the gold that I owe you.
$FF_SayPayDeny	I just don't have enough gold right now.
$FF_SaySellItems	I want you to sell some items for me.
$FF_SaySubmenu	I need a moment of your time. (NFF)
$FF_SaySubreturn	Never mind.
$FF_SayShake	Hey! Snap out of it! (fix glitch)
$FF_SayElope	I think you and I should always be together (Elope).
$FF_SayElopeYes	Yes, together forever.
$FF_SayElopeNo	On second thought. No.
$FF_SayTeach	I'd like to teach you a new spell.

$FF_LootingChooseOff	Don't loot anything.
$FF_LootingChoose0	Keep an eye out for Gold.
$FF_LootingChoose1	Keep an eye out for Ammo.
$FF_LootingChoose2	Keep an eye out for Food.
$FF_LootingChoose3	Keep an eye out for Potions.
$FF_LootingChoose4	Keep an eye out for Ingredients.
$FF_LootingChoose5	Keep an eye out for Miscellaneous.
$FF_LootingChoose6	Keep an eye out for Weapons/Ammo/Armor.
$FF_LootingChoose7	Keep an eye out for Armor.
$FF_LootingChoose8	Keep an eye out for Weapons.
$FF_LootingChoose9	Keep an eye out for Books.
$FF_LootingChoose10	Keep an eye out for Plants.
$FF_LootingChooseForget	Eh, never mind.

$FF_LootingChangeOff	I'd like you to loot something while you're with me.
$FF_LootingChange0	I'd like you to loot something different (currently: Gold).
$FF_LootingChange1	I'd like you to loot something different (currently: Ammo).
$FF_LootingChange2	I'd like you to loot something different (currently: Food).
$FF_LootingChange3	I'd like you to loot something different (currently: Potions).
$FF_LootingChange4	I'd like you to loot something different (currently: Ingredients).
$FF_LootingChange5	I'd like you to loot something different (currently: Miscellaneous).
$FF_LootingChange6	I'd like you to loot something different (currently: Weapons/Ammo/Armor).
$FF_LootingChange7	I'd like you to loot something different (currently: Armor).
$FF_LootingChange8	I'd like you to loot something different (currently: Weapons).
$FF_LootingChange9	I'd like you to loot something different (currently: Books).
$FF_LootingChange10	I'd like you to loot something different (currently: Plants).

$FF_SendLootChoose0	I want you to store loot in your Inventory.
$FF_SendLootChoose1	I want you to store loot in your Follower Storage.
$FF_SendLootChooseAlt1	I want you to store loot in your Clothing Satchel.
$FF_SendLootChoose2	I want you to store loot in the Player Chest.
$FF_SendLootChooseForget	I've changed my mind.

$FF_SendLootChange0	I want you to store loot in another place (currently: Inventory)
$FF_SendLootChange1	I want you to store loot in another place (currently: Follower Storage)
$FF_SendLootChangeAlt1	I want you to store loot in another place (currently: Clothing Satchel)
$FF_SendLootChange2	I want you to store loot in another place (currently: Player Chest)

$FF_OutfitChangeMenu	I'd like to change an outfit of yours.
$FF_OutfitCreateMenu	I'd like to create an outfit for you.

$FF_OutfitCreateBase	I'd like you to wear a standard outfit.
$FF_OutfitChangeBase	I'd like to change your standard outfit.
$FF_OutfitCreateTown	I'd like you to wear a town outfit.
$FF_OutfitChangeTown	I'd like to change your town outfit.
$FF_OutfitCreateHome	I'd like you to wear a home outfit.
$FF_OutfitChangeHome	I'd like to change your home outfit.

$FF_OutfitRemoveMenu	I'd like to remove an outfit.
$FF_OutfitRemoveBase	I'd like to remove your standard outfit.
$FF_OutfitRemoveTown	I'd like to remove your town outfit.
$FF_OutfitRemoveHome	I'd like to remove your home outfit.

$FF_OutfitSatchel	Open your clothing satchel.

$FF_RoleChange0	I'd like to change your combat role (currently: Standard)
$FF_RoleChange1	I'd like to change your combat role (currently: Healer)
$FF_RoleChange2	I'd like to change your combat role (currently: Tank)

$FF_RoleChoose0	I want you to take a balanced, standard role.
$FF_RoleChoose1	I want you to heal me and allies during combat.
$FF_RoleChoose2	I want you to taunt enemies to you during combat.
$FF_RoleChooseForget	On second thought, just keep your current role.

; SANDBOXING --
$FF_Sandbox	Sandboxing
$FF_Sandbox_0	Off
$FF_Sandbox_1	Allow
$FF_Sandbox_2	Allow/Autobox in Town
$FF_Sandbox_3	Allow/Autobox at Home
$FF_SandboxDS	Allow Followers to sandbox when the Player is inactive for a short while. Autobox causes followers to stay perpetually in a sandbox state while indoors in a town/city location or player home and in custom defined locations. It is AI Package-based.\n(Default: On)

$FF_AllowSandbox	Sandbox Style

$FF_RelaxRadius	Relax Radius
$FF_RelaxRadiusDS	The radius at which Followers will sandbox near the Player. The radius will gradually move as the player moves.\n(Default: 2048 units)

$FF_RelaxTime	Relax Idle Delay
$FF_RelaxTimeDS	The number of seconds that must pass while the Player is idle before a Follower will enter sandboxing mode.\n(Default: 5 seconds)

$FF_RelaxRamp	Relax Ramp-Up
$FF_RelaxRampDS	The number of seconds that must pass while the Player is moving (sprinting/running) before a Follower will stop sandboxing.\n(Default: 3 seconds)

$FF_RelaxAvoid	Relax Avoidance
$FF_RelaxAvoidDS	The distance at which a sandboxing Follower will automatically move away from the Player. If Followers seem to flee too often when you are near them, reduce this.\n(Default: 45 units)

$FF_ToggleFurn	Ignore Special Furniture
$FF_ToggleFurnDS	Followers will ignore special furniture that can be interacted with, such as forges, chopping wood and so on. They can still use idle markers.\n(Default: Off)

$FF_ToggleBoxdlg	Stop During Player Dialogue
$FF_ToggleBoxdlgDS	If enabled, Followers will stop sandboxing when the Player is enagaged in dialogue-based conversation. This is to simulate Followers paying attention to what is going on.\n(Default: Off)

$FF_ToggleTown	Only Sandbox in Town
$FF_ToggleTownDS	Followers only sandbox when in a city, town, dwelling or a Player-defined custom location.\n(Default: Off)

$FF_ToggleDungeon	Only Sandbox in Non-Dungeon
$FF_ToggleDungeonDS	Followers will only sandbox if the location is not flagged as a dungeon (via keyword).\n(Default: Off)

$FF_AutoboxExt	Autobox in Town Exteriors
$FF_AutoboxExtDS	Only valid if Autobox is active in the Sandbox dropdown above, this allows city, town and Player home exteriors to be auto sandboxed, without having to add them specifically to the Custom Location list.\n(Default: Off)

$FF_MultiBox	Multi-Level Sandboxing
$FF_MultiBoxDS	If enabled, allows Followers (and other NPCs) to sandbox between floors of multi-leveled structures. Affects a game setting.\n(Default: Off)

$FF_CustomBoxDS	Sets this area as a Custom Location that Followers will sandbox in when using Only Sandbox in Town or Auto Sandbox in Town Interiors.\n(Default: Off)

$FF_KeyTogBox	Toggle Sandbox Hotkey
$FF_KeyTogBoxDS	Set the key to used for toggling Sandboxing on and off. This can be used separately from the Command Follower ability.


; STEALTH --

$FF_Stealth	Stealth

$FF_ToggleStealth	Improved Stealth AI
$FF_ToggleStealthDS	Cause Followers to behave better when you are sneaking. They will not attack while you are sneaking unless they or you are struck in combat. It is AI Package-based with some scripting.\n(Default: On)

$FF_ToggleEnhSneak	Enhance Sneaking
$FF_ToggleEnhSneakDS	Followers who are sneaking with the Player are put into heightened stealth, making them nearly undetectable by enemies. REQUIRES Improved Stealth AI to be enabled.\n(Default: On)

$FF_Extinguish	Extinguish Torches when Stealthed
$FF_ExtinguishDS	When the Player is stealthing, torches will be removed from the inventories of followers. They are returned when the Player is out of stealth or enters combat. Only works on vanilla game torches. REQUIRES Improved Stealth AI to be enabled. Recommend OFF if you are using the Command All Followers manual version.\n(Default: Off)


; LOOTING
$FF_AutoLootHeader	Auto-Looting

$FF_LootMaxTime	Maximum Search Time
$FF_LootMaxTimeDS	The maximum amount of time followers can auto-loot, in seconds. Sneaking, Combat and Maximum Player Distance will still stop looting actions.

$FF_LootDelayCombat	Looting Delay After Combat
$FF_LootDelayCombatDS	This is the delay, in seconds, that looting takes place automatically after combat (if active).

$FF_LootDelay	Loot Start/Stop Delay
$FF_LootDelayDS	This is the delay, in seconds, when asking followers to loot by command (not automatically after combat).

$FF_LootPlayerDistance	Maximum Player Distance
$FF_LootPlayerDistanceDS	This is the maximum distance that a follower can be from the player when auto-looting. This is automatically reduced in interiors by 65% of the distance set.  Beyond this distance, looting will stop.

$FF_LootSpeed	Looting Speed
$FF_LootSpeedDS Speeds of movement of followers that are looting, which also can help speed up loot time.

$FF_LootPostCombat	Auto-Loot After Combat
$FF_LootPostCombatDS	If enabled, followers will engage in auto-looting when combat ends. If a follower is in bleedout state (downed), auto-looting will be delayed for 5 seconds to allow them to recover. It will then check a second time and if a follower is still downed, auto-looting will be cancelled. This fixes a bug where followers can loot each other.

$FF_LootDropJunk	Drop Misc Junk Items
$FF_LootDropJunkDS	If enabled, a looting follower will drop junk items to the ground if looting Misc items if they are under a certain gold value (next setting). Techically, we can't prevent filtering out these items during search. Dropped items are flagged as only being picked up by the player.

$FF_LootJunkVal	Junk Item Value
$FF_LootJunkValDS	This is the value, in gold, that a Misc item must be (minimally) for a looting follower to not drop an item.

$FF_KeyActAutoLoot	Start/Stop Auto-Loot Hotkey
$FF_KeyActAutoLootDS	Allows you to start auto-looting, causing followers to search the immediate area or to stop followers currently searching. If a follower is in bleedout (downed), auto-looting will be cancelled if they do not revive within 5 seconds. This a due to a bug where downed followers can be seen as lootable.

$FF_KeyTogLootCbt	Toggle Auto-Loot in Combat Hotkey
$FF_KeyTogLootCbtDS	Allows you to enable or disable auto-looting for all followers after combat. Can still be activated on-demand. Types of items looted are set individually for each follower, under the Tweaks section.

$FF_TogAutoLootOn	Auto-Loot Enabled
$FF_TogAutoLootOff	Auto-Loot Disabled
$FF_AutoLootStart	Start Auto-Looting
$FF_AutoLootStop	Stop Auto-Looting
$FF_AutoLootStartMsg	Followers are searching...
$FF_AutoLootStopMsg	Followers stopped searching


; TELEPORT --

$FF_CatchUp	Catch Up (Teleport)

$FF_ToggleWarp	Allow Teleport
$FF_ToggleWarpDS	Allow Followers to auto teleport to the Player when at or greater than the distance defined in "Catch Up Distance". Followers are teleported behind you. It does allow Followers to enter places they aren't normally allowed to.\n(Default: On)

$FF_WarpRange	Catch Up Distance
$FF_WarpRangeDS	Minimum distance required before catch up is activated.\n(Default: 2560 units)

$FF_WarpStart	Catch Up Time
$FF_WarpStartDS	Time that must pass before checking for catch up distance.\n(Default: 8 seconds)

$FF_WarpWait	Ask to Teleport Waiting Followers
$FF_WarpWaitDS	On-demand Teleport (via Command Power or Hotkey) allows you to summon waiting followers. You will receive a yes/no dialogue for each waiting follower.

$FF_KeyPort	Teleport Followers Hotkey
$FF_KeyPortDS	Set the key to used for teleporting Followers to you on demand. This can be used separately from the Command Follower ability. It does allow Followers to enter places they aren't normally to.

; MOVEMENT --

$FF_Movement	Movement

$FF_MoveSpeed	Movement Boost
$FF_MoveSpeedDS	Sets the speed value of all Followers to this value, in percent. Setting this value to the default of 100, will essentially turn off this feature. When turned off, individual Follower speeds (if above 100) will not change back to normal until a new game is loaded. You must exit the MCM for this change to be set.\n(Default: 100%)

$FF_DynamicMove	Dynamic Speed Adjustment
$FF_DynamicMoveDS	If enabled, Follower move speed is set to 100% and is boosted to the value set in Movement Boost when the Player is running/sprinting. Only occurs if the Player is not in combat, not in interior cells and the Followers are not sandboxing and greater than 768 units away. Dynamic speed does poll often when in use but only makes changes during the right conditions. You must exit the MCM for this change to be set.\n(Default: Off)

$FF_FleeDistance	Avoidance Proximity
$FF_FleeDistanceDS	The detection distance at which Followers will move out of your way (flee). If set too high, they will constantly avoid you.\n(Default: 12 units)

$FF_ProtectCell	Protect Followers when Changing Cells
$FF_ProtectCellDS	Occasionally if you have multiple followers with you, the game may accidentally place them inside of other objects or each other. When enabled, they will not take damage or register a hit event for 2 seconds after entering a new cell. This is recommended on unless you have some game issue with it.


; WAITING --

$FF_Waiting	Waiting

$FF_WaitNoBox	Wait Without Sandboxing
$FF_WaitNoBoxDS	If checked, Followers will no longer sandbox while commanded to wait, no matter what location they are in.\n(Default: Off)

$FF_WaitForever	Wait Forever
$FF_WaitForeverDS	If checked, Followers will wait where you tell them to forever. In other words, they will not follow Skyrim's rule where they are dismissed after 3 days. This will not work on custom followers with their own dialogue or followers that do not use the vanilla Wait/Follow command system.\n(Default: Off)

$FF_KeyFollowAll	Followers Wait/Follow Hotkey
$FF_KeyFollowAllDS	Set the key to toggle between follow and wait status on all followers. Looks at the first follower found for what to change to (follow or wait).


; MOUNTS --

$FF_Mounts	Mounts
$FF_MountsInvalid	Mounts (Dismount to Change)

$FF_MountStyle	Mount Support
$FF_MountStyleDS	Type of mount and riding support for Followers. No Support allows other mods to control all aspects, Spawned Horses provides mounts and riding packages, Riding Support Only provides riding packages and no mounts from NFF. It is AI Package-based.\n(Default: Spawned Horses)

$FF_HorseSkinGlobal	Global Horse Skin
$FF_HorseSkinGlobalDS	Set the default skin for all spawned Follower horses.\n(Default: Brown)

$FF_KeepHorse	Horses Stay Around
$FF_KeepHorseDS	Spawned horses now stick around after being dismounted.\n(Default: Off)


; PLAYER MOUNT --

$FF_PlayerHorse	Player Horse

$FF_KeyHorse	Call Player Horse Hotkey
$FF_KeyHorseDS	Set the key to be used to call the horse the Player has ridden last. Pressing 'ESC' will clear out the hotkey.
$FF_KeyHorseM	Call Player Horse

$FF_ToggleHorseRev	Spawn Horse Off-Camera
$FF_ToggleHorseRevDS	If the Player's horse is moved to the Player, attempt to spawn it off-camera.

$FF_ToggleHorseDis	Call Disables/Enables Nearby Horse
$FF_ToggleHorseDisDS	Using Call Horse while the player's horse is near, disables or enables it. It is NOT recommended to use this option with Immersive Horses or Convenient Horses installed.

; SPARRING --

$FF_SparHead	Sparring

$FF_SparAllow	Allow Sparring
$FF_SparAllowDS	Allows Sparring via Dialogue when talking to someone.
$FF_SparAny	Anyone Can Spar
$FF_SparAnyDS	Allows nearly anyone in the game to spar. Intent here is to allow you to test the might of import followers or other NPCs. BEWARE can be game breaking or possibly cause a riot if you do this without thinking. Only works on Unique persons, not flagged as Child. Any allies in area may help them, causing a riot.
$FF_SparVocal	Use Announcer
$FF_SparVocalDS	Allows a disembodied voice to announce the fight.
$FF_SparBrave	Brave Fighting
$FF_SparBraveDS	When Sparring, combatants are confident and will not run unless they feel outmatched.
$FF_SparStrip	Clothing Stripped
$FF_SparStripDS	Not serious and not immersive! Clothing damage trope added to sparring. Combatants can lose clothing when hit. Best with outfits and clothing that features 5 or more slots.
$FF_SparStripFX	Ripping Sounds
$FF_SparStripFXDS	Plays a ripping sound as an audible cue to when clothing parts are removed. There is no distinction between materials for the sound fx.

; sparring osd strings
$FF_SparTied	Match is tied
$FF_SparFollow	Combatant is following you
$FF_SparCancel	Match is cancelled

; sparring dialogue strings
$FF_SaySpar	Interested in doing some sparring?
$FF_SaySpar0	I'd like you to be the first combatant.
$FF_SaySparAlt0	I'd rather you be the first combatant.
$FF_SaySpar1	I'd like you to be the second combatant.
$FF_SaySpar2	Cancel the sparring match.


; COMBAT --

$FF_Combat	Combat

$FF_ReduceFight	Reduce Infighting
$FF_ReduceFightDS	Attempts to stop infighting between Followers in the case of friendly fire or area of effect spells and abilities. Does not eliminate accidental or incidental damage.\n(Default: On)

$FF_NoPTDamage	No Player Damage to Teammates
$FF_NoPTDamageDS	When active, player attacks, destruction spells and shouts (except Unrelenting Force) will not affect Followers or teammates. This applies a perk to the player, similar to the Dragonborn black book ability. Inventory side effect: while weapons/spells/fists are drawn, weapons may show zero damage.\n(Default: Off)

$FF_ToggleUnForce	Unrelenting Force Ignores Followers
$FF_ToggleUnForceDS	When active, Unrelenting Force will not affect Followers and teammates. Toggle this off if you want to use it to push them out of the way. Requires No Team Magic Damage to be installed and active.

$FF_CombatAware	Improved Combat Awareness
$FF_CombatAwareDS	If a follower has no target in combat, will attempt to find one in the area. It will first choose the player's target and if not one, will try to find a random target to engage. Does not affect followers with Confidence of Cautious or Cowardly.\n(Default: On)

$FF_EnsureCombatEnd	Ensure Combat Ends
$FF_EnsureCombatEndDS	Fix for an occasional game bug where the player is no longer in combat and there are no enemies but a follower gets stuck in a combat state.\n(Default: Off)

$FF_Protection	Protected Followers
$FF_ProtectionDS	With this setting enabled, Followers that are with you are flagged as Protected (can only be killed by you and will enter a bleedout state). With this option off, Followers can be killed by anyone (including you) and will not enter bleedout, if they are not Essential. Most Followers in the game (and downloaded) are Essential, hired guards and soldiers would not be. Changes take effect once the MCM menu is closed.\n(Default: On)


; BLEEDOUT --

$FF_Bleedout	Bleedout

$FF_BleedTime	Bleedout Time
$FF_BleedTimeDS	The time, in seconds, that an NPC will remain in bleedout before recovering. This affects all NPCs, not only Followers.\n(Default: 15 seconds)

$FF_ToggleBleed	Disable Bleedout Recovery
$FF_ToggleBleedDS	If enabled, Followers no longer recovery from a bleedout state during combat. You cannot affect them with potions or healing spells.\n(Default: Off)

$FF_ToggleRevive	Revive After Combat
$FF_ToggleReviveDS	Ensures that a Follower recovers from bleedout when both of you are no longer in combat. Helps smooth out instance where the game keeps them in bleedout.\n(Default: Off)

$FF_Potion_0	Off
$FF_Potion_1	Any (Weak to Strong)
$FF_Potion_2	Any (Strong to Weak)
$FF_Potion_3	Minor Healing
$FF_Potion_4	Healing
$FF_Potion_5	Plentiful Healing
$FF_Potion_6	Vigorous Healing
$FF_Potion_7	Extreme Healing
$FF_Potion_8	Ultimate Healing

$FF_AllowPotion	Potion Recovery
$FF_AllowPotionDS	You can use a healing potion on followers if at or below 50% health, or if they are bleeding out. The type of potion used is determined by the menu selection.\n(Default: Off)


; SHARING --

$FF_Sharing	Gold Sharing

$FF_PhatLoot	Share the Wealth
$FF_PhatLootDS	Randomly allows you to share big hauls of gold with your Followers, which gives them a morale boost for a short time (bonus health). Only occurs when looting from containers or dead bodies. Distributes half of the gold collected between your Followers.

$FF_PhatThreshold	Share Minimum
$FF_PhatThresholdDS	The minimum amount of gold that must be collected in order to evoke the sharing dialogue.

$FF_PhatRandom	Share Randomly
$FF_PhatRandomDS	Loot is shared randomly, depending on degree higher than the minimum you have set. If disabled, loot is always shared.

$FF_PhatAsk	Ask to Share
$FF_PhatAskDS	If enabled, a prompt is shown to share loot with your followers. Otherwise, loot is shared without your consent. Could cause false positives as not every container can be determined in every game circumstance.

$FF_NoGivenGold	No Given Gold
$FF_NoGivenGoldDS	If enabled, at any time that the Player shares gold with Followers via this mod, it will not appear in their inventory.


; REGARD --

$FF_RegardHeader	Regard System

$FF_UseRegard	Allow Regard
$FF_UseRegardDS	Allow Followers to use Regard system, which allows them to build a rapport with you. There are 9 ranks of Regard that are increased by spending time with them, fighting with them and sharing rewards.

$FF_RegardGifts	Allow Gift Giving (Rank 3)
$FF_RegardGiftsDS	Followers can give you gifts from time to time at Regard Rank 3 (checked daily, 33% chance). This usually consists of crafting materials (skins, base metals, gems). Only occurs while they are in your service.\n(Default: On).

$FF_RegardGiftInterval	Gift Interval
$FF_RegardGiftIntervalDS	The number of days that must pass before a follower will give you a gift.

$FF_RegardCourage	Allow Courage Ability (Rank 6)
$FF_RegardCourageDS	Followers have enhanced Courage at Rank 6. Spells that cause fear, only briefly affect them.\n(Default: On).

$FF_RegardInspired	Allow Inspired Ability (Rank 9)
$FF_RegardInspiredDS	Followers are inspired while in your service at Rank 9. Their ranged, weapon and destruction skills are raised by 10 and they receive a bonus of 25 to health and stamina.\n(Default: On).


; ROLE ADJUSTMENTS --

$FF_HealRoleAdj	Healer Role

$FF_HealChance	Heal Check Chance
$FF_HealChanceDS	The chance, during combat, of a healer checking to see if someone needs to be healed. Checked in 4-second intervals. Reducing this value will cause the healer to be more likely to fight or perform other actions.
$FF_HealThresh	Heal Magnitude Multiplier
$FF_HealThreshDS	You can set a multiplier to reduce or increase the amount of healer given by a follower in the Healer Role, when using NFF's healing spell. The heal spell normally heals 75 + (20% of Restoration skill) + (healer's level). Set at 100%, it does this amount. At 50%, it would do half this amount.

$FF_HealPlayerVal	Player Healing Percent
$FF_HealPlayerValDS	The percentage at which a Healer Role Follower is likely to heal the Player when in the Healer Role. Setting this to 0 will cause the Healer to not heal the player.
$FF_HealSelfVal	Self Healing Percent
$FF_HealSelfValDS	The percentage at which a Healer Role Follower is likely to heal themselves when in the Healer Role. Setting this to 0 will cause the Healer to not heal themselves (this only disables scripted healing).
$FF_HealOtherVal	Other Healing Percent
$FF_HealOtherValDS	The percentage at which a Healer Role Follower is likely to heal other party members when in the Healer Role. Setting this to 0 will cause the Healer to not heal other party members.

$FF_notifyHeal	Player Healed Notification
$FF_notifyHealDS	Display a message when a Follower in the Healer Role heals the Player.\n(Default: On)

$FF_notifyHealOther	Follower Healed Notification
$FF_notifyHealOtherDS	Display a message when a Follower in the Healer Role heals another Follower.\n(Default: On)

$FF_TankRoleAdj	Tank Role
$FF_TauntChance	Taunt Check Chance
$FF_TauntChanceDS	The chance, during combat, of a tank taunting during combat. Checked in 4-second intervals only if the taunt cooldown has expired. Reducing this value will cause the tank to be more likely to fight or perform other actions.

$FF_ToggleTauntVis	Disable Taunting Visual
$FF_ToggleTauntVisDS	Disables the visual effect when a Follower in the Tank role taunts. You may wish to deselect this if taunting causes objects to fly around in your game.\n(Default: Off)

$FF_notifyTaunt	Tank Taunted Notification
$FF_notifyTauntDS	Display a message when a Follower in the Tank Role uses their taunt ability.\n(Default: On)


; MAGIC --

$FF_Magic	Magic

$FF_Charge_0	Off
$FF_Charge_1	Use Soul Gems
$FF_Charge_2	Auto Recharge

$FF_AllowCharge	Weapon Recharging
$FF_AllowChargeDS	Allow Followers to periodically charge weapons they are using. Use Soul Gems uses filled soul gems in their inventory (not Player-filled, game limitation). Auto Recharge automatically recharges weapons with a bonus based on their Enchanting skill.\n(Default: Off)

$FF_notifyCharge	Weapon Recharged Notification
$FF_notifyChargeDS	Display a message when a Follower recharges their weapon, has used a soul gem or cannot use a gem that was traded to them (Weapon Recharging must be enabled).\n(Default: On)

$FF_LightStyle	Candlelight Style
$FF_LightStyleDS	If taught the Candlelight spell, this is the default style of light a follower will cast. Follower versions of Candlelight last 3 minutes. You can set this to "Do not cast" to have no followers cast light by default.

; SUMMONING --

$FF_Summoning	Minions

$FF_MinionSupport	Minion Support
$FF_MinionSupportDS	Allows the Framework to support up to 10 summoned/reanimated creatures cast by the Player or Followers. This "captures" the creature to reduce infighting from occuring with them. Up to 5 creatures can be captured per individual cast. If using No Team Magic Damage, creatures will not take damage from Follower or Player spells. This can cause a "false positive" and grab minions summoned by other NPCs.

$FF_MinionFollows	Minions Follow
$FF_MinionFollowsDS	If Summoned Creature Support, above, is enabled, they will follow the player. This fixes an issue where a minion may get struck accidentally by the player or followers and just stand there. It is possible that this will cause "false positive" captures to follow the player as well.

$FF_notifyMinion	Acquiring Minion Notification
$FF_notifyMinionDS	Display a message when a summoned/reanimated creature has been acquired and supported by the framework. Requires Summoned Creature Support to be active.\n(Default: Off)


; MENTORING --

$FF_TeachHeader	Mentoring & Teaching

$FF_LearnSpells	Learn Spells From Books
$FF_LearnSpellsDS	Followers can learn new spells if you trade books with them. They must have the magicka to cast a spell to learn it. The book is destroyed if the Follower learns its spell.\n(Default: Off).

$FF_TeachSpells	Teach Spells You Know
$FF_TeachSpellsDS	Followers can learn new spells that you have readied in your left or right hand. They must have the magicka to cast a spell to learn it. This requires targeting the Follower with the Command ability.\n(Default: Off).

$FF_notifyLearn	Spells Learned Notification
$FF_notifyLearnDS	Display a message when a Follower learns a spell or is unable to (Learn Spells from Books must be enabled).\n(Default: On)

$FF_SkillAffinity	Allow Skill Affinity
$FF_SkillAffinityDS	By fighting alongside your Followers, you are able to learn new techniques and insights from them, allowing you to raise your own skills. This is a weighted system, meaning that you are more likely to learn skills from Followers who are more skilled than you are. Only certain skills are eligible (weapon, armor and magic skills) and only if the Follower has a rating over 15 in that skill.

$FF_SkillAffinityMod	Affinity Chance Modifier
$FF_SkillAffinityModDS	This is the base chance that you will learn a skill from a Follower. It is increased if their skill is higher than yours, otherwise the base chance is used. 12% is the default chance, which will give a fairly decent chance of raising your skills.


; SELLING --

$FF_Selling	Selling

$FF_SellThreshold	Sell Items Threshold
$FF_SellThresholdDS	The maximum time that a Follower can be away from the party when selling items for the Player.\n(Default: 1 Hour)


; MAIN DIALOGUES --

$FF_Dialogue	Main Dialogue Features

$FF_AllowGuard	Expendable Recruits
$FF_AllowGuardDS	Gives you a chance to recruit non-essential NPCs as Followers by bribing them. The more gold you offer, the more likely they will join you.\n(Default: On)

$FF_DlgDivorce	Divorce Spouse
$FF_DlgDivorceDS	Enable this option to have the ability to divorce your spouse via dialogue. Jilted Followers will leave your service and won't talk to you for 4 in-game hours. Not recommended to use with multi-spouse mods.\n(Default: Off)

$FF_DlgElope	Elope
$FF_DlgElopeDS	When enabled, this option gives an addditional dialogue to potential spouses, allowing you to marry them immediately, without a ceremony or requring an Amulet of Mara.(Default: Off)

$FF_DlgSteward	Dismiss Steward
$FF_DlgStewardDS	Shows a dialogue that allows you to dismiss a Hearthfires steward when talking to them.\n(Default: Off)

$FF_DlgBlades	Blade Recruitment Support
$FF_DlgBladesDS	Adds additional supports to asking Delphine to recruit blades. It uses the Framework's count instead of the game's follower count. Blades must be in the Game Slot for this to work properly.


; EXTRA DIALOGUES --

$FF_SubDialogue	Extra Dialogue Features (sub-menu)

$FF_DlgSubmenu	Framework Submenu
$FF_DlgSubmenuDS	This option shows a dialogue that features all the dialogues in this section. Toggle this off to completely hide the submenu.

$FF_DlgSell	Sell Items
$FF_DlgSellDS	Shows a dialogue on Followers that will allow them to sell items for the Player.\n(Default: On)

$FF_DlgTeach	Teach Spells Dialogue
$FF_DlgTeachDS	Shows a dialogue on Followers that will allow the Player to teach them spells, if that Gameplay option is enabled.\n(Default: Off)

$FF_DlgBehind	Get Behind Me
$FF_DlgBehindDS	Shows a dialogue on Followers that cause them to move behind you (teleport).\n(Default: Off)

$FF_DlgShake	Snap Out of It
$FF_DlgShakeDS	Shows a dialogue on Followers that may help with animation glitches, such as running in place or turning different directions rapidly.\n(Default: Off)

$FF_AllowExpel	Expel Follower
$FF_AllowExpelDS	For debugging purposes, this shows an Expel dialogue that forces a Follower to be removed from the framework and add or removes them from the correct Factions. Only applies to non-Imported Followers. Can be used in place of normal dismss dialogue in other cases.\n(Default: Off)


; HIRING --

$FF_Hiring	Hiring

$FF_HireCost	Initial Weekly Follower Cost
$FF_HireCostDS	The initial cost to hire a Follower, in gold, per week. This affects all newly recruited Followers. You can set different values for each follower on the stats page. If you cannot pay a Follower, she will eventually leave your service. Imported Followers are an exception as NFF cannot affect their recruitment or dismissal.\n(Default: 0 gold)

$FF_ExpendCost	Expendables Cost
$FF_ExpendCostDS	The maximum cost of hiring an Expendable Recruit. Mid-range and low-range values are calculated based on the maximum cost.\n(Default: 250 gold)


; CHATTER --

$FF_Chatter	Idle Chatter

$FF_Chatter_0	On
$FF_Chatter_1	Off
$FF_Chatter_2	Sandboxing

$FF_SetChatter	Idle Chatter Enabled
$FF_SetChatterDS	Sets Idle Chatter for Followers on, off or only when sandboxing. Does not affect Imported Followers. It is AI Package-based.\n(Default: On)

$FF_SetChatterFreq	Idle Chatter Frequency
$FF_SetChatterFreqDS	Sets Idle Chatter frequency for Followers, in 15 minute increments, up to a maximum of 8 hours (480 minutes). Setting this to 0 will use the default time (1 hour for vanilla, random for RDO.\n(Default: 0 - Disabled)

$FF_AllowHellos	Allow Greetings
$FF_AllowHellosDS	Allow Followers to say hellos/greetings to the player while recruited.
$FF_AffectHellos	Affect Greeting Distance
$FF_AffectHellosDS	Unlocks the abililty to affect the game's greeting distance. This affects ALL NPCs, not just followers.
$FF_HelloDistance	Minimum Greeting Distance
$FF_HelloDistanceDS	Allows you to set the minimum distance that an NPC will greet with player. If you set this to 0, NPCs will not greet you. This INCLUDES followers, regardless of the Allow Greetings setting, above.

; PLAYER CHEST --

$FF_PlayerChest	Extra Storage

$FF_KeyPlaceChest	Place Player Chest Hotkey
$FF_KeyPlaceChestDS	Allows the player to move a chest to them that only they can access as additional, protected storage. Cannot be placed in dungeons. Can be moved around in cities, towns and home bases (main area) at will. Otherwise only can be moved once per 4 hours, in game.
$FF_KeyPlaceChestM	Place Player Chest

$FF_KeyOpenChest	Open Player Chest Hotkey
$FF_KeyOpenChestDS	Allows the player to open the Player Chest remotely in cities, towns and home bases (main area) at will. Anywhere else in the game this is restricted to once per 12 hours (game time).
$FF_KeyOpenChestM	Open Player Chest

$FF_DisableStorage	Disable Extra Inventory
$FF_DisableStorageDS	Enables or disables inventory globally on all followers. This only hides the menu entry.

; IMPORT --

$FF_Import	Follower Import

$FF_DlgAllowImport	Allow Import/Export Dialogue
$FF_DlgAllowImportDS	Shows a dialogue when talking to a follower that will allow you to import or export her from NFF. Import generally only checks if a follower is in the game's follower faction and if they are a player teammate. If only a player teammate the assumption is made that you can import them to allow them to borrow features of NFF. There can easily be false-positives so use your better judgement.

$FF_DlgImport	Confirm Import/Export
$FF_DlgImportDS	If enabled, show a confirmation message when importing or exporting Followers.\n(Default: On)

$FF_DlgImportSet	Recommend Import Tweaks
$FF_DlgImportSetDS	If enabled, will show one or more dialogues upon importing a follower, allowing you to apply "safe" settings to them. Does not guarantee compatibility. Only shown once per unique import follower. If disabled, it will work silently once on each unique import follower, setting recommended safeguard settings.\n(Default: On)

$FF_AutoImpGen	Auto-Import/Export
$FF_AutoImpGenDS	Supports auto-import and export for other imported followers, depending on detected changes to Player Teammate flag. Shows a dialogue on import or export one-time (per importable follower) that allows you to teach NFF to auto import/export them. Use your best judgment based on if you dismissed them or not. Selecting no with exclude them from import or export (individually set). Follows Follower Count settings for checking purposes.

$FF_AutoImpSerana	Auto-Import Serana
$FF_AutoImpSeranaDS	Supports auto-import for Serana, depending on changes in her own game script. Follows Follower Count settings for checking purposes. Note that auto-export is already built-in for Serana. However, if she is auto-imported, you will not get export dialogue when speaking to her.


; BEHAVIOR --

$FF_BehaviorBase	Behavior Defaults

$FF_SetAggrBase	Aggression
$FF_SetAggrBaseDS	Aggression of Followers when they are in combat. Aggression is not affected outside of combat.
$FF_SetAsstBase	Assistance
$FF_SetAsstBaseDS	Base combat assistance of Followers.
$FF_SetConfBase	Confidence
$FF_SetConfBaseDS	Base combat bravery of Followers.
$FF_SetMoralBase	Morality
$FF_SetMoralBaseDS	The base type of crimes Followers will commit and support if the Player commits them.


; CRAFTING/INTERACTION --

$FF_CraftingBase	Crafting/Interaction Defaults

$FF_CraftTorchesBase	Create Torches
$FF_CraftTorchesBaseDS	When enabled, newly acquired Followers can create torches by default. See Follower Tweaks for specifics.\n(Default: Off)

$FF_CraftArrowsBase	Create Arrows
$FF_CraftArrowsBaseDS	When enabled, newly acquired Followers can create arrows by default. See Follower Tweaks for specifics.\n(Default: Off)

$FF_CraftPotionsBase	Create Potions
$FF_CraftPotionsBaseDS	When enabled, newly acquired Followers can create potions by default. See Follower Tweaks for specifics.\n(Default: Off)

$FF_SharpWeaponsBase	Sharpen Weapons
$FF_SharpWeaponsBaseDS	When enabled, newly acquired Followers can sharpen weapons by default. See Follower Tweaks for specifics.\n(Default: Off)

$FF_DrinkTavernBase	Drink at the Tavern
$FF_DrinkTavernBaseDS	When enabled, newly acquired Followers can interact with wenches and order drinks in a tavern.\n(Default: Off)

$FF_DoDrunk	Allow Drunk Effect
$FF_DoDrunkDS	If enabled and you have Drink at the Tavern allowed for a Follower, they have a chance to get drunk while drinking.

$FF_PlayerInteract	Allow Player Interaction
$FF_PlayerInteractDS	Allows Vanilla-voiced Followers (and some expanded from RDO) to comment on some Player activities. Can be turned off for individual Followers under Tweaks. Currenly only supports player leveling up and crafting at the forge.\n(Default: On)

$FF_AllowForge	Allow Extra Craftables
$FF_AllowForgeDS	Allows you to craft additional items at the forge, such as: Candlelight Tome, Hidden Helmet, Ignore Token and separate Hood for Serana.\n(Default: On)


; QUESTS --

$FF_Tracking	Follower Tracking

$FF_AllowTracking	Allow Tracking
$FF_AllowTrackingDS	Adds a quest to the Miscellaneous Quest Journal that allows you to track Followers on the map.


; COMPANION QUESTS --

$FF_Companions	Optional Companions
$FF_CompSaadia	Saadia
$FF_CompSaadiaDS	Allow Saadia as a companion once "In My Time of Need" is completed. Also allows you to marry her. (May require location change once complete)\n(Default: Off)
$FF_CompYsolda	Ysolda
$FF_CompYsoldaDS	Allow Ysolda as a companion once you are friends (brought her a Mammoth Tusk, for example. May require location change once complete).\n(Default: Off)
$FF_CompWinter	Winterhold Mages
$FF_CompWinterDS	Allow Colette, Drevis, Faralda, Nirya, Phinis, Sergius and Tolfdir as Followers once you have become the Archmage of Winterhold College. You may also marry them. RDO (or similar) is required for full functionality. (May require location change once complete)\n(Default: Off)
$FF_CompThieves	Thieves Guild Members
$FF_CompThievesDS	Allow Tonilia, Sapphire, Cynric, Niruin, Rune, Thyrnn and Vipir as Followers once you have defeated Mercer. You may also marry them. RDO (or similar) is required for full functionality. (May require location change once complete)\n(Default: Off)


; DIFFICULTY --
$FF_DifficultyHead	Game Difficulty Override
$FF_AllowDiff	Allow Difficulty Override
$FF_AllowDiffDS	Allows you to override the Player's damage dealt and Player's damage received multipliers on the current game difficulty. Switching difficulty will reset any changes. In SSE, not sure if this setting has any conflicts with CC Survival Mode.
$FF_PlayerDamageOutDS	Change the multiplier to damage that the Player deals to enemies. Switching difficulty will reset any changes.
$FF_PlayerDamageInDS	Change the multiplier to damage that the Player receives from enemies. Switching difficulty will reset any changes.

$FF_Diff0	Novice
$FF_Diff1	Apprentice
$FF_Diff2	Adept
$FF_Diff3	Expert
$FF_Diff4	Master
$FF_Diff5	Legendary


; ABILITIES --

$FF_Abilities	Player Casted Abilities

$FF_AllowCmd	Command Followers
$FF_AllowCmdDS	You can send commands, dismiss, trade, set outfits and other actions for individual (or all) Followers.\n(Default: On)

$FF_AllowCalm	Calm Followers
$FF_AllowCalmDS	Allows you to have the Calm Followers power. This ability will calm all Followers and teammates and immediately remove them from combat. Lasts 60 seconds, affects a fairly large area.\n(Default: Off)
$FF_AllowRetreat	Followers Retreat
$FF_AllowRetreatDS	Allows you to have the Followers Retreat power. This ability will cause all followers to retreat from battle. Lasts 30 seconds, affects a huge area.\n(Default: Off)

; NOTIFICATIONS --

$FF_Notify	Notifications

$FF_notifyStartup	Startup Tasks Notification
$FF_notifyStartupDS	Display Framework startup messages when first installing the mod or loading an existing game.\n(Default: On)
$FF_notifyHelm	Headwear Storage Notification
$FF_notifyHelmDS	Display a message when a Follower stores a headwear item (Headwear only in Combat must be enabled).\n(Default: On)
$FF_notifyInteract	Interactions Notification
$FF_notifyInteractDS	Display a message when a Follower interacts with other NPCs, such as buying drinks at a tavern.\n(Default: On)

; MOD SUPPORT --

$FF_ModSupport	Mod Support
$FF_GenSupport	SOT Genesis
$FF_GenSupportDS	Automatically adds FriendFlower ingredient to follower inventories if Genesis is installed and active. This allows Genesis to create extra spawns when followers are around.

; DEBUG --

$FF_NoActor	No Actor
$FF_Invalid	None
$FF_NotInScene	Not In Scene

$FF_Debug	Debugging (NPC in Crosshair)

$FF_DebugTarget	Actor Name
$FF_DebugTargetDS	Currently targeted actor.

$FF_DebugMod	Actor Mod
$FF_DebugModDS	The name of the mod that the object reference (in-game instance) is from.

$FF_DebugScene	Quest (Scene)
$FF_DebugSceneDS	The name of the quest running a scene on this NPC, if any.
$FF_DebugSceneMod	Quest Mod
$FF_DebugSceneModDS	The name of the mod that is currently running a scene quest on NPC, if any.

$FF_DebugPackage	AI Package
$FF_DebugPackageDS	The hex code of the currently running AI Package, if any. The first two digits of this code are equal to the the mod in your load order.
$FF_DebugPackMod	AI Mod
$FF_DebugPackModDS	The name of the mod that is currently running an AI package on this NPC, if any.
$FF_DebugPackQuest	AI Quest
$FF_DebugPackQuestDS	The Quest that owns the currently running AI Package, if any. This only shows information if a quest explcitly owns a package.

$FF_ClickPurge	Click to Purge
$FF_DebugExit	Purge on Exit
$FF_ClickHere	Click Here
$FF_MCMExit	Exit MCM to Apply
$FF_MCMExitBox	Please completely exit the MCM to apply this change.
$FF_ResetExit	Reset on Exit
$FF_SetExit	Set on Exit
$FF_MCMOk	Ok

$FF_ResetImport	Purge NPC
$FF_ResetImportDS	Removes a targetted Follower from the framework. Imported Followers will not be dismissed. NPC must be under the crosshair prior to going into the MCM menu.

$FF_ForceFollower	Force Follower
$FF_ForceFollowerDS	Force this actor to be in the Follower faction and/or the Marriage Faction if they have valid voices for those. Does support RDO added voices. ONLY use this on NPCs that are not normally available as followers. Using this to circumvent completing a quest to obtain a follower or to "fix" a normal follower may result in issues with that actor as a follower. This is NOT follower Import.
$FF_NoForceFollower	Cannot Force Follower

$FF_ImportEn	Import Enabled
$FF_ImportDisDS	Toggles between allowing or not allowing this NPC to be imported using NFF's dialogues.

$FF_ForceMarry	Force Marry/Elope
$FF_ForceMarryDS	Force this actor to be in the Marriage Faction if they have valid voices for those. Does support RDO added voices. If a valid voice is not found, you can still elope with them (you will not have home choices). DO NOT USE on quest NPCs until you have completed all quests that involve them.
$FF_NoForceMarry	Cannot Force Marry/Elope

; CONFIGURATION --

$FF_Config	Save/Load Configuration
$FF_SaveConfig	Save to File
$FF_SaveConfigDS	Saves global settings (Interaction and System values) to a file that can be recalled later. Does not save the settings for individual Followers. You no longer need to save your game for this to take effect.
$FF_LoadConfig	Load from File
$FF_LoadConfigDS	Load global settings (Interaction and System values) from a file that you have previously saved.
$FF_ConfigLoaded	Settings Loaded. Please exit the MCM menu to apply all changes.
$FF_ConfigSaved	Settings Saved.
$FF_ConfigError	PapyrusUtil needs to be installed to Save/Load Configuration.

; SAVE/LOAD TWEAKS

$FF_Tweaks	Save/Load Follower Settings
$FF_SaveTweaks	Save Follower Settings
$FF_SaveTweaksDS	Save settings of the currently selected follower to a json file. Saves all tweaks, traits and basic equipment hiding features. Only supports Unique followers.
$FF_LoadTweaks	Load Follower Settings
$FF_LoadTweaksDS	Load settings of the currently selected follower from a saved json file.

$FF_SaveAllTweaks	Save All Current Followers
$FF_SaveAllTweaksDS	Save the settings of all current followers to individual json files. Only supports Unique followers.
$FF_AutoSaveTweaks	Auto-Save on Dismiss
$FF_AutoSaveTweaksDS	Automatically saves Unique followers when they are dismissed or exported.

$FF_NotFound	Not Found

$FF_TweaksLoaded	Follower Settings Loaded.
$FF_TweaksSaved	Follower Settings Saved.


; HOTKEYS --

$FF_GroupKeys	Follower Action Keybinds

$FF_KeyCmd	Command Followers Hotkey
$FF_KeyCmdDS	Set the key to be used for the Command Followers Ability. You can uncheck the casted version if you are using a hotkey. Pressing 'ESC' will clear out the hotkey.

$FF_KeyInfo	NPC Info Hotkey
$FF_KeyInfoDS	Set the key to be used to get information about the NPC, such as level, class, health and so on. This is somewhat more useful when used on a current follower.

$FF_KeyAttack	Followers Attack Hotkey
$FF_KeyAttackDS	Cause Followers to Attack the enemy in direct line of sight of the player or the enemy the player is currently targetted. Cancels retreat behavior.

$FF_KeyRetreat	Followers Retreat Hotkey
$FF_KeyRetreatDS	Cause Followers to Retreat from battle. Use second time to cancel retreat. Lasts 45 seconds or until cancelled.

$FF_KeyCalm	Calm Followers Hotkey
$FF_KeyCalmDS	Set the key to be used for the Calm Ability. You can uncheck the casted version if you are using a hotkey. Pressing 'ESC' will clear out the hotkey.

$FF_KeyBehindAll	Followers Behind You Hotkey
$FF_KeyBehindAllDS	Set the key to place all followers in front of you behind you. Fires a short range effect that affects all followers close to you.

$FF_KeyTrade	Trade Items Hotkey
$FF_KeyTradeDS	Set the key to used for bringing up the trading menu with a follower. This can be used at a distance.






$FF_KeyClone	Clone Outfit Hotkey
$FF_KeyCloneDS	Set the key to used for cloning the outfit of a targetted Follower. This can be used at a distance.
$FF_KeySell	Sell Items Hotkey
$FF_KeySellDS	Set the key to used for having a Follower sell items for you. This can be used at a distance.


$FF_KeyHistoryMenu	History Menu Hotkey
$FF_KeyHistoryMenuDS	Shows a history menu, using SkyUILib, where you can select a past follower and either teleport to them or teleport them to you.

$FF_KeyFavoritesMenu	Favorites Menu Hotkey
$FF_KeyFavoritesMenuDS	Shows the favorites menu, using SkyUILib, where you can select a favorite follower that you have previously stored and either teleport to them or teleport them to you.




$FF_NotifyGetLoot	Follower Looted Notification
$FF_NotifyGetLootDS	Display a message when a Follower that is set to auto-loot picks up an item.\n(Default: On)
$FF_NotifyDropLoot	Follower Dropped Loot Notification
$FF_NotifyDropLootDS	Display a message when a Follower that is set to auto-loot drops an item.\n(Default: On)

$FF_Yes	Yes
$FF_No	No


; CORE --

$FF_Core	Core

$FF_RealCount	Real-Time Follower Count
$FF_RealCountDS	Check Follower Count in real-time (recommended enabled). If disabled, you can check count manually in NFF's Extras menu.\n(Default: On).

$FF_UseConsole	Enable ConsoleUtil
$FF_UseConsoleDS	This option will allow the Framework to check for ConsoleUtil (Skyrim) or ConsoleUtilSSE. This optional SKSE enhancement is only required for Leveling Followers via the MCM and for Healer casting animations. If disabled and you do not have ConsoleUtil installed, you will not have checking errors in Papyrus.

$FF_UseColorMsg	Allow Colored Notifications
$FF_UseColorMsgDS	Shows colorized notification messages using SkyUILib. If you are using UI Scaling or Tweaking mods and the text is too large for you, turn this option off.\n(Default: Off).

$FF_ResetFolQuest	Restart Main Quests
$FF_ResetFolQuestDS	If checked while you exit the MCM menu, this will restart and reset the vanilla Follower quest and the import Followers quest and non-imported Followers will be dismissed. Solely for troubleshooting purposes.

$FF_MenuStyle	In-Game Menu Style

$FF_UseEnhMenu	Use Enhanced Menus
$FF_UseEnhMenuDS	Replaces the Command Followers Ability menus with enhanced menus from SkyUILib. The enhanced menus include more features than the vanilla menus can reasonably allow.\n(Default: On).

$FF_MenuStopTime	Stop Time in Enhanced Menus
$FF_MenuStopTimeDS	While an enhanced menu is activity, the passage of time is stopped. This can help if NPCs are moving while in the menu system.\n(Default: Off).


; -- ALL FOLLOWER TABS --

$FF_Follower	Follower

$FF_ViewActor	Viewing
$FF_PickActorDS	Fine-tune individual settings for this Follower.

$FF_NoFollowers	No Followers

; -- FOLLOWER TWEAKS TAB --

$FF_FollowerActions	Follower Actions

$FF_ShowExtras	Show Extra Information
$FF_ShowExtrasDS	Toggle to show extra information on this page. Currently only supports crafting cooldowns. This stays toggled across all followers.\n(Default: Off)

$FF_ToggleBoxFac	Allowed to Sandbox
$FF_ToggleBoxFacAlt	Allowed to Sandbox*
$FF_ToggleBoxFacDS	Allow this Follower to sandbox. This can conflict with followers that have their own sandboxing function or are designed to do other things during "downtime". It is AI Package-based.\n(Default: On)

$FF_SetChatterFol	Allow Idle Chatter
$FF_SetChatterFolDS	Sets Idle Chatter for this Follower on, off or only when sandboxing. If the main Idle Chatter setting is set to Off, this setting will be ignored. It is AI Package-based.\n(Default: On)

$FF_ToggleStealthFac	Allow Stealth AI
$FF_ToggleStealthFacAlt	Allow Stealth AI*
$FF_ToggleStealthFacDS	Allow this Follower to use improved out of combat stealth movement. Could conflict if a follower has their own stealth package outside of combat. It is AI Package-based.\n(Default: On)

$FF_SetLooting	Auto-Looting
$FF_SetLootingDS	Allows this follower to auto-loot certain types of items. Occurs when the player is not moving, not sneaking and doesn't have weapon/magic drawn. This is tied into NFF's follow package, so a follower will need to be using that. Also, it may be helpful to increase sandbox ramp-up time to 10 seconds or more to give them time to loot.

$FF_SendLoot	Send Loot to
$FF_SendLootDS	If auto-looting is enabled, allow you to choose between sending that loot to the follower's inventory, her follower storage (if in use) or the player chest.

$FF_AllowInventory	Allow Follower Inventory
$FF_AllowInventoryDS	If enabled, this follower has access to additional inventory storage. This storage is temporary, in that it only lasts while the follower is recruited, hired or imported. Once dismissed, all items in additional follower inventory are sent to the Player Chest.

$FF_SetRange	Set Follow Range
$FF_SetRangeDS	Distance that the Follower follows the Player when out of combat. It is AI Package-based.\n(Default: Medium)

$FF_ToggleBaseFollow	Use Default Follow
$FF_ToggleBaseFollowAlt	Use Default Follow*
$FF_ToggleBaseFollowDS	If enabled, the Follower will not use the Framework's follow package and instead use their default follow package. For basic Followers, this is the vanilla package. For imported Followers, this is the follow package that comes with them.

$FF_ToggleBaseCombat	Use Default Combat
$FF_ToggleBaseCombatAlt	Use Default Combat*
$FF_ToggleBaseCombatDS	If enabled, the Follower will not use the Framework's combat package (including range) or combat style. They will instead use combat package and style as defined in the package that comes with them. For basic followers, this is Skyrim's default combat package list.

$FF_AnimalInventory	Allow Inventory (Animal/Mech Only)
$FF_AnimalInventoryDS	If enabled, you can trade with this animal or mechanical (Dragonborn) Follower, just like other Followers. Trading equipment to them may cause them to equip it, but it will not be visible on them.

$FF_LightStyleFac	Candlelight (Follower)
$FF_LightStyleFacDS	If taught the Candlelight spell, this is the default style of light this follower will cast. You can set this to "Do Not Cast" to prevent this follower from casting light. This works completely independent from the setting you have for all followers.

$FF_FollowerMount	Follower Mount
$FF_FollowerMountInvalid	Follower Mount (Dismount to Change)

$FF_ToggleHorseFac	Allow Horse
$FF_ToggleHorseFacAlt	Allow Horse*
$FF_ToggleHorseFacDS	If disabled, the Follower will not spawn a horse but still uses riding packages. Turn off if a follower has their own custom horse spawning ability or package. It is AI Package-based.\n(Default: On)

$FF_HorseSkinFol	Follower Horse Skin
$FF_HorseSkinFolDS	Set the skin for this Follower's spawned horse.\n(Default: Brown)

$FF_HorseFXFol	Follower Horse FX
$FF_HorseFXFolDS	Apply an Effect to the Follower's spawned horse.\n(Default: None)

$FF_CombatF	Follower Combat

$FF_SetRole	Combat Role
$FF_SetRoleAlt	Combat Role*
$FF_SetRoleDS	Sets the Follower's role in combat. Default, Healer and Tank are the possible choices at this time. May conflict with followers that have their own taunt or healing AI packages. It is AI Package-based for Healer Role.

$FF_TauntSound	Taunt Sound
$FF_TauntSoundDS	Customize the type of voice when the Follower uses a Taunt in Tank mode.
$FF_Taunt_0	Male (Average)
$FF_Taunt_1	Male (High)
$FF_Taunt_2	Male (Low)
$FF_Taunt_3	Female (Average)
$FF_Taunt_4	Female (High)
$FF_Taunt_5	Female (Low)
$FF_Taunt_6	Unvoiced

$FF_SetCStyle	Combat Style
$FF_SetCStyleAlt	Combat Style*
$FF_SetCStyleDS	Change the Combat Style of this Follower. This affects offensive, defensive, circling and strafing movement/AI in combat and weapon type choices (magic, ranged, melee and/or staff). Default is the Combat Style provided with the Follower. It is AI Package-based.
$FF_SetCStyle_0	Follower is using their native combat style or the vanilla default, if no style is defined.
$FF_SetCStyle_1	Follower is using Mercenary, which emphasizes melee. An in your face, warrior style, that is more offensive than defensive.
$FF_SetCStyle_2	Follower is using Defender, which emphasizes melee. Will try to stick to an enemy, but is defensive over being offensive.
$FF_SetCStyle_3	Follower is using Berserker, which emphasizes offensive melee. Able to wield a weapon in each hand.
$FF_SetCStyle_4	Follower is using Archer, which emphasizes ranged but is capable of some melee. Decent at strafing ranged attacks.
$FF_SetCStyle_5	Follower is using Ranger, which is a decent mix of ranged and melee. They can use a weapon in each hand but will switched to range when possible.
$FF_SetCStyle_6	Follower is using Spellsword, which is a mix of melee and magic, with some staff use.
$FF_SetCStyle_7	Follower is using Wizard, which is the traditional offensive magic, with a bit of staff use. Good at strafing and holding back to use spells.
$FF_SetCStyle_8	Follower is using Magician, which is a mage build that uses spells but will favor staff use, given than one is in their inventory.
$FF_SetCStyle_9	Follower is using Priest, which is a defensive mage build with some staff use. Good at holding back and acting defensively.
$FF_SetCStyle_10	Follower is using Balanced, which is pretty fairly divided with regards to offense, defense and what weapons they will use.
$FF_SetCStyle_11	Follower is using Arcane Archer, which emphasizes ranged but is capable of some melee and magic. Decent at strafing ranged attacks.
$FF_SetCStyle_12	Follower is using War Priest, which emphasizes melee but can drop into ranged or magic use to some degree, if available. Will try to stick to an enemy, but is defensive over being offensive.

$FF_SetClass	Class
$FF_SetClassAlt	Class*
$FF_SetClassDS	Change the Class of this Follower. Classes provide the base skill weights and Health/Magicka/Stamina weights that an NPC uses. It does not provide nor affect Perks and Spells. If you change the Class of a Follower it is PERMANENT. You cannot restore it's original class unless it is provided in this list. Classes not in the list show in parenthesis. Requires ConsoleUtil.

$FF_SetClassWarn	*Warning*\n\nUsing this feature to change a Follower's class is PERMANENT. You cannot restore a Follower with a custom class to it's original class. It WILL wipe any skill edits with NFF, if you have made those. It cannot be used on Non-unique actors because their base class cannot be detected.\n\nThis message will only be shown once.

$FF_SetCbtRange	Set Combat Range
$FF_SetCbtRangeDS	Distance that the Follower follows the Player when in combat.\n(Default: Medium)

$FF_DefenseStance	Defensive Stance
$FF_DefenseStanceDS	If enabled, this follower uses a defensive stance in combat. They will only attack if they or the player have been attacked (struck in combat). Is reset if Follower or player drop out of combat.\n(Default: Off)

$FF_NoCombat	No Combat State
$FF_NoCombatDS	Forces the Follower to be completely defensive. They will not engage in combat and stay near the player. If in the healer role, they will continue to heal. They cannot taunt. Due to the player teammate flag, they will still draw weapons. They will act rather lifeless in this state. Useful if you have a pet follower, healer-only follower or pack mule.\n(Default: Off)

$FF_WerewolfChange	Werewolf Transformation
$FF_WerewolfChangeDS	Allows you to set this follower to turn into a werewolf after receiving a certain amount of damage in combat (threshold, below).

$FF_WerewolfThresh	Werewolf Change Threshold
$FF_WerewolfThreshDS	The amount of damage (in percent of overall health) that the follower must take before changing into a werewolf.

$FF_EnforceRange	Enforce Combat Range
$FF_EnforceRangeDS	While in combat, this ensures that followers maintain Combat Range from the player if they are not attacking or casting spells. This is helpful for getting followers out of corridors and other mischief. Activing this option will also apply it to captured minions.

$FF_DamageMult	Damage Multiplier
$FF_DamageMultDS	Changes the damage multiplier of the Follower, affecting how much damage they can do overall. If SPID is installed and you have chosen the magic mod, will also link this multiplier to Destruction Spell and Shout Magnitude.

$FF_DamageMultFixed	Fixed Damage Multiplier
$FF_DamageMultFixedDS	Set this follower to have a fixed damage multiplier that stays at the value that you set on this page, regardless of the global damage multiplier.

$FF_DamageMultAll	Dynamic Damage Multiplier
$FF_DamageMultAllDS	Changes the damage multiplier of any recruited, imported or hired follower to the set value. If SPID is installed and you have chosen the magic mod, will also link this multiplier to Destruction Spell and Shout Magnitude. Once a follower is dismissed or exported, their multiplier changes back to x1.00. You can set a Fixed Damage Multiplier under Tweaks.

$FF_FollowerPack	Follower System
$FF_PackHigh	Package Priority
$FF_PackHighDS	This sets a Follower to use High-Priority versions of the Framework's Packages. This affects Sandboxing, Waiting, Mounting Up, Riding, Improved Stealth, Bump-Into, Following, Healer Role and Combat Styles, which are package-delivered. If a Follower is not using those in most (nearly all) circumstances, use this option. DO NOT toggle this On unless Necessary as it can possibly affect other mods that deliver follower features.\n(Default: Off)
$FF_Pack_1	Standard (50)
$FF_Pack_2	High (70)
$FF_Pack_3	Very High (99)

$FF_AutoImpReset	Reset Auto-Import/Export
$FF_AutoImpResetDS	Click this option to reset Auto Import and Export setting for this imported follower. Will show the yes/no dialogues again, allowing you to change your decision. Requires Auto-Import/Export to be active.
$FF_AutoImpResetDlg	Follower Auto Import and Export has been reset.

$FF_FollowerProt	Follower Protection

$FF_BaseEssential	Actor is Essential (Base Form)
$FF_BaseNonUnique	Actor is Ineligible (Not Unique)
$FF_SetEssential	Set to Essential
$FF_SetEssentialAlt	Set to Essential*
$FF_SetEssentialDS	Set this Follower to Essential or reverse the process.\n(Default: Off)

$FF_Crafting	Crafting

$FF_CraftMax	When Depleted
$FF_CraftTime	When Able To

$FF_CraftTorches	Can Create Torches
$FF_TorchTime	Crafts Torches
$FF_CraftTorchesAlt	Can Create Torches*
$FF_CraftTorchesDS	When sandboxing, allows the Follower to create torches if she is running low on them. This only occurs when she is in the vicinity of a forge. It has a cooldown of 8 (in-game) hours.\n(Default: Off)

$FF_CraftArrows	Can Create Arrows
$FF_ArrowTime	Crafts Arrows
$FF_CraftArrowsAlt	Can Create Arrows*
$FF_CraftArrowsDS	When sandboxing, allows the Follower to create extra arrows (instead of bolts) of a lesser quality than are available to the Player. The higher the Archery skill, the more they will make at one time. This only occurs when she is in the vicinity of a forge. It has a cooldown of 8 (in-game) hours.\n(Default: Off)

$FF_CraftBolts	Can Create Bolts
$FF_BoltTime	Crafts Bolts
$FF_CraftBoltsAlt	Can Create Bolts*
$FF_CraftBoltsDS	When sandboxing, allows the Follower to create steel bolts instead of arrows. The higher the Archery skill, the more they will make at one time. This only occurs when she is in the vicinity of a forge. It has a cooldown of 8 (in-game) hours.\n(Default: Off)

$FF_CraftPotions	Can Create Potions
$FF_PotionTime	Crafts Potions
$FF_CraftPotionsAlt	Can Create Potions*
$FF_CraftPotionsDS	When sandboxing, allows the Follower to create potions, their potency based on the Player's level. The higher the Alchemy skill, the more they will make at one time. This only occurs when she is in the vicinity of an alchemy station. It has a cooldown of 8 (in-game) hours.\n(Default: Off)

$FF_SharpWeapon	Can Sharpen Weapons
$FF_SharpenTime	Sharpens Weapons
$FF_SharpWeaponAlt	Can Sharpen Weapons*
$FF_SharpWeaponDS	When sandboxing, allows the Follower to temporarily improve their weapons for a minor damage buff (+1). This only occurs when she is in the vicinity of a sharpening wheel. It has a cooldown of 6 (in-game) hours.\n(Default: Off)

$FF_Interaction	Interaction
$FF_TavernInteract	Drink at Tavern
$FF_TavernInteractAlt	Drink at Tavern*
$FF_TavernInteractDS	When sandboxing, allows the Follower to interact with innkeepers and tavern wenches, allowing them to order and consume drinks. This occurs randomly, from the time they enter the tavern to up to an hour or so later. They can order multiple drinks over time and occasionally have "one too many", causing them to become drunk for a short period.\n(Default: Off)
$FF_PlayerInterFac	Player Interaction
$FF_PlayerInterFacDS	Allows this Follower to make comments at the Player for certain activities. Only valid if they have a vanilla/RDO-expanded voice and Allow Player Interaction is enabled.\n(Default: On)
$FF_RegardFac	Can Use Regard
$FF_RegardFacDS	Follower is allowed to use the Regard system.
$FF_ResetRegard	Reset Regard
$FF_ResetRegardDS	Click to reset the Regard Rank of this Follower, restoring it to its starting value.


; -- FOLLOWER STATS TAB --

$FF_Stats	Base Stats

$FF_sLevel	Level
$FF_sLevelDS	Click to raise this Follower's level to that of the Player (requires ConsoleUtil for Skyrim or ConsoleUtilSSE for Special Edition) in order to work. You can use the optional bat file to do this as well. Target the follower in the console and type: bat nfflevel. This will allow them to continually level with the Player and only needs to be done one time, per unique follower.
$FF_sLevelUp	Follower level has been set.
$FF_sHealth	Health
$FF_sHealthDS	Click to change the value of the Health stat. This modifies the current value (just like an the bonus from wearing an enchanted item).
$FF_sMagicka	Magicka
$FF_sMagickaDS	Click to change the value of the Magicka stat. This modifies the current value (just like an the bonus from wearing an enchanted item).
$FF_sStamina	Stamina
$FF_sStaminaDS	Click to change the value of the Stamina stat. This modifies the current value (just like an the bonus from wearing an enchanted item).
$FF_sSkillDS	Click to change the value of the selected skill. This modifies the current value (just like an the bonus from wearing an enchanted item).
$FF_sMove	Movement Speed

$FF_Behavior	Behavior
$FF_SetAggression	Aggression
$FF_SetAggressionAlt	Aggression*
$FF_SetAggressionDS	Aggression of the Follower while in combat. May conflict with Followers with specifically designed AI features.
$FF_SetAssistance	Assistance
$FF_SetAssistanceAlt	Assistance*
$FF_SetAssistanceDS	Who a Follower will help in combat. May conflict with Followers with specifically designed AI features.
$FF_SetConfidence	Confidence
$FF_SetConfidenceAlt	Confidence*
$FF_SetConfidenceDS	The Follower's bravery in combat. May conflict with Followers with specifically designed AI features.
$FF_SetMorality	Morality
$FF_SetMoralityAlt	Morality*
$FF_SetMoralityDS	The types of crimes a Follower will commit and support if the Player commits them. May conflict with Followers with specifically designed AI features.

$FF_RegardHead	Follower Regard
$FF_RegardRank	Regard Rank
$FF_RegardPoints	Regard Points

$FF_FollowerCostHead	Follower Gold Cost
$FF_FollowerCost	Weekly Rate
$FF_FollowerCostDS	The cost to retain this Follower, per week, in gold.
$FF_FollowerZero	Free

$FF_StatEdit	Allow Stat Editing
$FF_StatEditDS	Toggles the ability to edit Health, Magicka, Stamina and Skills of Followers. Changes are NOT PERMANENT and last until the Follower gains a level.
$FF_Skills	Skills

$FF_pArchery	Archery
$FF_pOneHand	One-Handed
$FF_pTwoHand	Two-Handed
$FF_pLightArmor	Light Armor
$FF_pHeavyArmor	Heavy Armor
$FF_pBlocking	Blocking
$FF_pAlteration	Alteration
$FF_pConjuration	Conjuration
$FF_pDestruction	Destruction
$FF_pEnchanting	Enchanting
$FF_pIllusion	Illusion
$FF_pRestoration	Restoration
$FF_pAlchemy	Alchemy
$FF_pSneak	Sneak

; -- FOLLOWER PERKS TAB --

$FF_NoPerks	No Perks

; -- FOLLOWER ABILITIES TAB --

$FF_NoAbilities	None
$FF_AbilitiesBase	Base Spells & Abilities
$FF_AbilitiesBaseCost	Base Spells & Abilities / Cost
$FF_AbilitiesGranted	Granted Spells & Abilities
$FF_AbilitiesGrantedCost	Granted Spells & Abilities / Cost

$FF_RemoveSpellDS	Click to remove this granted spell. Will not remove spells that are part of Perk effects. Use your best judgement here when dealing with spells that come with a particular follower.
$FF_RemoveConfirm	Are you sure you wish to remove this spell?

$FF_Resist	Resistances

; -- FOLLOWER EQUIPMENT TAB --

$FF_EquipTweaks	Equipping Actions

$FF_SeranaHoodOff	Disable Serana's Hood
$FF_SeranaHoodOffDS	Enable this option to keep the game from constantly creating a hood for Serana and applying it to her.

$FF_ToggleHelmFac	Headwear only in Combat
$FF_ToggleHelmFacDS	Follower only wears headwear while in combat. May conflict with Followers with specific hood or helm features (Serana is supported, however).\n(Default: Off)

$FF_NoHelm	Never Equip Headwear
$FF_NoHelmDS	Follower never equips headwear. More useful for Followers that have a helmet as part of their default outfit and you wish to hide it. May conflict with Followers with specific hood or helm features.\n(Default: Off)

$FF_askHelm	Use the currently equipped head item\nas the Follower's Stored Headwear?

$FF_ToggleShieldFac	Shield only in Combat
$FF_ToggleShieldFacDS	Follower only uses shield while in combat. May conflict with Followers with specific shield equipping features\n(Default: Off)

$FF_ToggleAmmoFac	Auto Unequip Quiver
$FF_ToggleAmmoFacDS	Follower removes quiver when unequipping a bow or crossbow. Supports modded arrows and bolts (trade these items with any Follower at least once to include them).\n(Default: Off)

$FF_MenuAmmo	Ammo Supported
$FF_MenuAmmoDS	Read-only list of ammo supported by the framework. List applies to all Followers.

$FF_ToggleWeaponFac	Weapons only in Combat
$FF_ToggleWeaponFacDS	Follower only uses weapons while in combat or if the Player does not have his weapon drawn. They will be completely hidden, otherwise.\n(Default: Off)

$FF_RefreshWeaponFac	Refresh Weapons After Combat
$FF_RefreshWeaponFacDS	Refresh the follower's weapon after combat (unequip then re-equip it). Can help with odd weapon bugs or followers not fighting. Useful when follower is using a 2-handed weapon\n(Default: Off)

$FF_BaseOutfit	Base Outfit

$FF_CloneOutfit	Copy Outfit
$FF_CloneOutfitDS	Create a duplicate of this Follower's outfit. Take care to only click once as items are placed in your inventory.

; OUTFIT DEFAULTS -- (changed)

$FF_OutfitExclude	Show Outfit Dialogue
$FF_OutfitExcludeDS	If checked, custom outfit menu items will show for this follower. Otherwise it is hidden. Toggling this off doesn't restore a follower to their original outfit. It just hides being able to affect them.

$FF_OutfitBase	Outfit Settings (Global)

$FF_SetsUsed	Outfits in Use
$FF_SetsUsedDS	Click to view a list of all actors that have outfits assigned.

$FF_ShowGearSlots	Show Body Slots
$FF_ShowGearSlotsDS	If enabled, Body Slots are shown for Outfits (slower to load page).\n(Default: Off)

$FF_ViewGear	Outfit Preview Mode
$FF_ViewGearDS	If enabled, allows you to preview an outfit, as if you were trading with a follower. This does move their inventory in and out of a container temporarily. \n(Default: Off)

$FF_CustomHomeLocAdd	Not a Home Location
$FF_CustomHomeLocRem	Is a Home Location
$FF_CustomHomeLocDS	Add or remove this location as a location that is appropriate for Home Outfit use. A location with the keyword "Player Home" cannot be changed. A location with the name "Tamriel" is a generic location and cannot be changed. Some areas will not have locations and thus cannot be affected.

$FF_SwitchStyle	Outfit Switch Style
$FF_SwitchStyleDS	Allows you to choose how outfits switch for current followers. Auto changes automatically, based on the location. Toggle changes to the outfit most appropriate for the location and then back to standard/default if used again. Menu gives you a choice of outfits and will stay in that choice until you change it.
$FF_SwitchStyle_0	Auto Switch
$FF_SwitchStyle_1	Toggle Switch
$FF_SwitchStyle_2	Menu Switch

$FF_SwitchHotkey	Outfit Switch Hotkey
$FF_SwitchHotkeyDS	Allows you to define a hotkey for switching outfits of current followers. Only applies to Toggle or Menu switch types.

$FF_SwitchMenu	Outfit Switch
$FF_SwitchMenuDis	Outfit Switch (Disabled)

$FF_AutoGearScan	Scan Area for Outfit Switch
$FF_AutoGearScanDS	Enable this to scan former followers in the loaded area to set their outfits to be appropriate for the location the player is in. Not required if former recruits have only a base outfit and not required for followers that are with you.

$FF_DlgEquip	Show Outfit Dialogue (General)
$FF_DlgEquipDS	Show Custom Outfit dialogue when speaking to a Follower.\n(Default: On)

$FF_DlgEquip2	Outfit Dialogue on Main Menu
$FF_DlgEquip2DS	If enabled, outfit dialogue is shown right on the main dialogue menu. If unchecked, it is shown in NFF's submenu.

$FF_KeySetGear	Create Outfit Hotkey
$FF_KeySetGearDS	Set the key to used for creating or changing the Outfit for a targeted Follower. This can be used at a distance. Only applies a standard outfit.
$FF_KeyRemoveGear	Remove Outfit Hotkey
$FF_KeyRemoveGearDS	Set the key to used for removing the Outfit for a targeted Follower. This can be used at a distance. Only applies a standard outfit.

; GEAR SETTINGS (GLOBAL) --

$FF_GearBase	Gear Settings (Global)

$FF_RefreshWeapons	Refresh Weapons
$FF_RefreshWeaponsDS	Fixes an occasional game bug where weapons are not recognized correctly on a follower when loading a game. This only happens on game load and takes an extra second or two to trade weapons away from each follower, return them and re-equip them.\n(Default: On)

$FF_ToggleDraw	Disable Weapon Draw
$FF_ToggleDrawDS	Followers do not draw weapons when you draw yours.\n(Default: Off)

$FF_TorchExpire	Follower Torches Expire
$FF_TorchExpireDS	Normally, Follower torches last indefinately. Enabling this option will cause torches to last for one-hour (game time) and then expire. Like Player torches, cooldown on torches is reset when they are unequipped, if less than the expiration time.\n(Default: Off)

$FF_KeyRedress	Undress/Redress Hotkey
$FF_KeyRedressDS	Set the key to used for redressing a targetted Follower. Redress will check and reapply Headwear, Shield and Quiver settings. This can be used at a distance.


$FF_FollowerOutfits	Follower Outfits

$FF_Outfits_0	Standard Outfit
$FF_Outfits_1	Town Outfit
$FF_Outfits_2	Home Outfit
$FF_Outfits_3	Default Outfit

$FF_OutfitsDS_0	This is the standard, custom outfit worn by the follower, overriding their default outfit.
$FF_OutfitsDS_1	The follower's town outfit, worn in cities and town locations.
$FF_OutfitsDS_2	The outfit worn in the player home location or any location defined as a player home.
$FF_OutfitsDS_3	The follower's default outfit, that comes as part of their default form. No items listed means that the follower is naked if no armor or clothing items are in their inventory.

; status
$FF_OutfitActive	<font color='#42F09D'>In Use</font>
$FF_OutfitActiveBase	<font color='#5CB6E0'>In Use</font>
$FF_OutfitInactive	<font color='#F05951'>Unused</font>


$FF_GearList	Outfit Item List

$FF_OutfitItems	Items Shown

$FF_GearStyle_0	Standard
$FF_GearStyle_1	Town
$FF_GearStyle_2	Home
$FF_GearStyle_3	Default


; -- HOME BASES TAB --

$FF_NoBase	None
$FF_NoBaseName	(None)
$FF_PickBase	Pick Base
$FF_PickActor	Pick Actor
$FF_NoResidents	No Residents

$FF_homeHeader	Home Base

$FF_createBase	Create Base

$FF_createBaseDS	Create a new home base.
$FF_selBase	Select/Create Base
$FF_selBaseDS	Allows you to create a new home base (if None is shown in the list) or select an existing home base to view or edit it.
$FF_nameBase	Rename Base
$FF_nameBaseDS	Change the display name of the home base that is currently being viewed.

$FF_setLocHeader	View/Set Locations
$FF_homeBaseLoc	Home/Base
$FF_homeLoc	Home
$FF_setHomeLocDS	Allows you to set (or change) the home location of the selected home base to where you are currently standing. Followers assigned to this base will spend time in this location when not working or relaxing. You must exit the MCM for this change to be set.
$FF_renHomeLocDS	Change the display name the home location of the selected home base. Only affects what is displayed.
$FF_remHomeLocDS	Remove the home location of the selected home base. WARNING: This will remove the selected base entirely along with any work or relax location assigned to it. Any Followers assigned this base will return to their previous homes.

$FF_workLoc	Work
$FF_setWorkLocDS	Allows you to set (or change) the work location of the selected home base to where you are currently standing. Followers will travel to and spend time in this location from 8am to 4pm. You must exit the MCM for this change to be set.
$FF_renWorkLocDS	Change the display name the work location of the selected home base. Only affects what is displayed.
$FF_remWorkLocDS	Remove the work location of the selected home base.

$FF_playLoc	Relax
$FF_setPlayLocDS	Allows you to set (or change) the relax location of the selected home base to where you are currently standing. Followers will travel to and spend time in this location from 6pm to 2am. You must exit the MCM for this change to be set.
$FF_renPlayLocDS	Change the display name the relax location of the selected home base. Only affects what is displayed.
$FF_remPlayLocDS	Remove the relax location of the selected home base.

$FF_folBaseHeader	Add/Remove Follower
$FF_pickCurrent	Follower
$FF_pickCurrentDS	Allows you to pick a Follower currently with you in order to add them to or remove them from a home base.

$FF_addFolBase	Add to Current Base
$FF_addFolBaseDS	Assigns the currently displayed Follower to the home base you have selected. They will also switch bases if already assigned to one.

$FF_resHeader	Assign/Remove Residents
$FF_selBaseAct	Base Resident
$FF_selBaseActDS	Allows you to pick a Follower that is assigned to the selected home base in order to remove them or assign them to a different base.

$FF_destBase	Destination Base
$FF_destBaseDS	Allows you to create a new home base (if None is shown in the list) or select an existing home base to view or edit it.
$FF_moveBaseAct	Move to Base
$FF_moveBaseActDS	Moves the selected Follower from their current home base to the one shown in destination. If current and destination bases are set to the same, you can Refresh the base to try to fix any issues with residents.
$FF_refreshBaseAct	Refresh Base

$FF_removeBase	Remove
$FF_removeBaseDS	Remove the currently displayed Follower from any Home Base they are assigned to.

$FF_popHeader	Population
$FF_popTotal	Total Followers at All Bases
$FF_popBase	Followers at the Selected Base

$FF_remLocHeader	Remove Locations
$FF_nameLocHeader	Rename Locations

$FF_visitLocHeader	Visit Locations
$FF_resLocation	Resident Location

; HOME TWEAKS

$FF_HBTweaks	Home Base Tweaks (Global)
$FF_HBOwner	Take Ownership
$FF_HBOwnerDS	Allows you to take ownership of cells in which you have set a home base, work or relax location. Only works in interior cells for now. Also is able to scan the area for beds and allow you to take ownership of those. You are always asked first. Experimental Feature.

$FF_HBWorkStart	Work Start Time
$FF_HBWorkStartDS	Time that followers will start in their working location. Applied to all Home Bases.
$FF_HBWorkEnd	Work End Time
$FF_HBWorkEndDS	Time that followers will stop working. Applied to all Home Bases.
$FF_HBRelaxStart	Relax Start Time
$FF_HBRelaxStartDS	Time that followers will start in their relaxing location. Applied to all Home Bases.
$FF_HBRelaxEnd	Relax End Time
$FF_HBRelaxEndDS	Time that followers will stop relaxing. Applied to all Home Bases.
$FF_HBSleepStart	Sleep Start Time
$FF_HBSleepStartDS	Time that followers will start sleeping when NOT working or relaxing. Applied to all Home Bases.
$FF_HBSleepEnd	Sleep End Time
$FF_HBSleepEndDS	Time that followers will stop sleeping. Applied to all Home Bases.

$FF_OwnCell	You now own this cell


; -- SLOTS/HISTORY TAB --

$FF_FollowerCount	Number of Followers Allowed
$FF_FollowerCountDS	Allows you to set the hard limit of followers that are supported by the framework. The minimum is 2, maximum is 10.\n(Default: 10)
$FF_CountChangeWarn	Setting a value lower than the current follower count will remove/export all current followers.\nContinue?

$FF_slotHeader1	Slot/Follower
$FF_slotHeader2	Sorting

$FF_GameSlotRem	Remove from Game Slot
$FF_GameSlotRemDS	Remove this follower from Skyrim's original game slot, placing it in the first one available. Takes effect after closing the MCM.
$FF_GameSlotSend	Send to Game Slot
$FF_GameSlotSendDS	Send this follower to Skyrim's original game slot. Only recommended if you absolutely need to do this. Examples include getting married, recruiting Blades or a mod that only recognizes this slot. This should not be a permanent placement and only when you need to. Takes effect after closing the MCM.

$FF_SortSlots	Sort Follower Slots
$FF_SortSlotsDS	Sorts Follower Slots from high to low, filling in the gaps. Will also clear the Game Slot, if in use. Takes effect after closing the MCM.
$FF_FlushSlots	Flush Follower Slots
$FF_FlushSlotsDS	Clears out all Follower Slots, removing any Followers from those slots. Takes effect after closing the MCM.

$FF_KickActorDS	Select this Follower to toggle between removing them from this slot. Will also attempt to flush this slot of an invalid actor. Takes effect after closing the MCM.

$FF_histHeader	Follower History
$FF_histActor	Follower
$FF_histActorDS	List of Followers that have previously been in your company.
$FF_histLoc	Location
$FF_histLocDS	The current whereabouts of the former Follower. Click this location to fast travel to them. "Tamriel" is a catch-all for an unnamed worldspace. Changes applied when you exit the MCM menu.
$FF_histPort	Summon
$FF_histPortClick	Call to you
$FF_histPortDS	Summon this Follower to you. Changes applied when you exit the MCM menu.
$FF_histLength	History Length
$FF_histLengthDS	Set the history length (number remembered) from 0 to 100. Setting to 0 disables history.
