$_ih_Title	Immersive Hunting
$_ih_PageConfig	Settings
$_ih_Animation	Animations
$_ih_Support	Support
$_ih_Features	Extras
$_ih_Started	STATUS: STARTED
$_ih_Stopped	STATUS: STOPPED
$_ih_Status	START/STOP:
$_ih_LootMode	Loot Mode

$_ih_StartMod	START MOD
$_ih_StopMod	STOP MOD
$_ih_Process	Process
$_ih_RemoveArrow	Retrieve arrows
$_ih_Skin	Skin
$_ih_Harvest	Harvest
$_ih_Butcher	Butcher
$_ih_Extract	Extract
$_ih_PossibleAnimations	Possible animations to play
$_ih_SheatheWeapons	Sheathe weapons
$_ih_ForceThirdPerson	Force third person
$_ih_ForceThirdPersonOff	Disabled
$_ih_ForceThirdPersonOn	Just force
$_ih_ForceThirdPersonOnAndReturn	Force and return
$_ih_RequireDagger	Require dagger
$_ih_DaggerPosition	Dagger position
$_ih_DaggerAnkle	Ankle
$_ih_DaggerBackHip	Back hip
$_ih_UpdateDagger	Use last equipped dagger
$_ih_EnablePickup	Enable pick up
$_ih_EnablePickupAnim	Enable pick up animations
$_ih_EnablePlaceTorch	Place torch on ground
$_ih_EnableCampfire	Cooking animation for Campfire
$_ih_EnableDispose	Can dispose carcass
$_ih_EnableShovelBury	Shovel Bury Bodies
$_ih_EnableRealisticSkin	Realistic skinning
$_ih_EnableDisplay	Displays
$_ih_IEDNotInstalled	Immersive Equipment Displays is not installed
$_ih_EnableSoulsSupport	Skyrim Souls support
$_ih_EnableQuickLootSupport	QuickLoot support
$_ih_EnableRequireBottle	Requires bottle
$_ih_EnableBowAnim	Animations with bow
$_ih_Search	Search
$_ih_Dispose	Dispose
$_ih_Vanilla	Vanilla
$_ih_Prompt	Prompt

$_ih_StartModDesc	Start or stop Immersive Hunting Animations.
$_ih_LootModeDesc	Select the loot mode when interacting with carcasses.\nVanilla: The inventory menu is opened; after removing an item, the corresponding animation will play.\nPrompt: A prompt with options to choose from based on the items present in the carcass; after choosing an option, the corresponding animation will play.\nProcess: All items will be looted from the carcass and an unique animation will play, if applicable.
$_ih_ProcessDesc	Toggle to enable animations when processing/removing all items from carcasses.
$_ih_EnableRemoveArrowDesc	Toggle to enable animations when removing arrows from carcasses.
$_ih_EnableSkinDesc	Toggle to enable animations when removing pelts from carcasses.
$_ih_EnableHarvestDesc	Toggle to enable animations when removing materials from carcasses.
$_ih_EnableButcherDesc	Toggle to enable animations when removing food items from carcasses.
$_ih_EnableExtractDesc	Toggle to enable animations when removing potion/poison items from carcasses.
$_ih_PossibleAnimationsDesc	Select the number of possible animations to play from a single carcass. Used only in Loot mode: Vanilla.
$_ih_ForceThirdPersonDesc	Select the options to force(or not) third person camera when performing one of the animated actions in first person.
$_ih_SheatheWeaponsDesc	Toggle to sheathe weapons when interacting with carcasses.
$_ih_EnableDisplayDesc	Toggle to enable displays for daggers and hunting materials.
$_ih_RequireDaggerDesc	Toggle to require the use of a dagger (your last equipped one) when performing any of the actions that use it. If no dagger is present, then your character will use a rock (found on the ground) or their claws, if a Khajiit or Argonian.
$_ih_DaggerPositionDesc	Select the dagger position to be used during the animations (and IED displays).
$_ih_UpdateDaggerDesc	Toggle to use last equipped dagger when interacting with carcasses.
$_ih_EnablePickupDesc	Toggle to enable carcass pick up. When this is enabled, you will be able to carry some carcasses while using the grab function (holding Activate).
$_ih_EnablePlaceTorchDesc	Toggle to place the current carried torch on the ground next to the player when performing one of the animated actions.
$_ih_EnableCampfireDesc	Toggle to enable the cooking animation for "Campfire - Complete Camping System".
$_ih_EnableDisposeDesc	Toggle to enable the disposing of carcasses when interacting in Loot mode: Prompt or Loot mode: Process.
$_ih_EnableShovelBuryDesc	Toggle to use the functionality from "Shovels Bury Bodies" when disposing a carcass.
$_ih_EnableRealisticSkinDesc	Toggle to enable the realistic skinning system. After skinning certain carcasses, their models will be update (skin removed). If Hunting in Skyrim is installed, your character gains XP and skinning stats.
$_ih_IEDNotInstalledDesc	Immersive Equipment Displays is not installed. Displays option is unavailable.
$_ih_EnableSoulsSupportDesc	Toggle to enable Skyrim Souls unpaused menus support.
$_ih_EnableQuickLootSupportDesc	Toggle to enable QuickLoot support.
$_ih_EnableRequireBottleDesc	Toggle to require bottles when extracting poisons, for Alchemy Requires Bottles.
$_ih_EnableBowAnimDesc	Toggle to play animations when your character has a bow equipped.
$_ih_RequiresBottle	You need an empty bottle to store the venom!